[{"version": "1", "index": 0, "hash": "26ea5d22048bccf41385f4bd5b489148", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vez", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "time (specific occurrence)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 1, "hash": "aa15457d671c87e3ebd6367a0ed022b9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "a\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "year"}, {"version": "1", "index": 2, "hash": "68f0477021c4ca1c4a8d6e095afa7140", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tiempo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "time (general),  weather"}, {"version": "1", "index": 3, "hash": "9ae6e063e269320735c1f470d68c4179", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "d\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "day"}, {"version": "1", "index": 4, "hash": "12703dd1411c33587da2004a9434a400", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cosa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "thing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 5, "hash": "cadd04f831fb7466ae95243f08a4aa3e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hombre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "man"}, {"version": "1", "index": 6, "hash": "4d2aa37ecdd52b899359c0ffbaa8402a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "parte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "part,  portion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 7, "hash": "d1fded22db9fc8872e86fff12d511207", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vida", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "life"}, {"version": "1", "index": 8, "hash": "2b2f4507ee9dcedd17456cc9b5f735b2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "momento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "moment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 9, "hash": "a05be3f47b0befe1bc3693f4d5caab03", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "forma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "form,  shape,  way"}, {"version": "1", "index": 10, "hash": "202447d5d44ce12531f7207cb33b6bf7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "casa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "house"}, {"version": "1", "index": 11, "hash": "dd485e41f1758def296e1bc7377f8ea7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mundo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "world"}, {"version": "1", "index": 12, "hash": "c1d9e760f410b0de86305f5b0fe13bfa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mujer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "woman,  wife"}, {"version": "1", "index": 13, "hash": "56240cdbe63405c3bb76e007e5160143", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "case,  occasion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 14, "hash": "dedd48b9fdedb80e6028359b8fb120e7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pa\u00eds", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "country"}, {"version": "1", "index": 15, "hash": "744497f0c75423cda00167c9dcd71dac", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lugar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "place,  position"}, {"version": "1", "index": 16, "hash": "8e406feab23e1239a50b0d329b0754fb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "persona", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "person"}, {"version": "1", "index": 17, "hash": "12c3de998cc272112872ea8a1c2f67b9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hora", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hour,  time (specific)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 18, "hash": "f3f7b8890bc68c5efaa1e563899e6f13", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "trabajo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "work,  job,  effort"}, {"version": "1", "index": 19, "hash": "dbf8386ad34c7bac0e3f5f712756bfae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "punto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "point,  dot,  period"}, {"version": "1", "index": 20, "hash": "5b4d762427d4dff75f6e5885cb380080", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mano", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hand"}, {"version": "1", "index": 21, "hash": "5a169ca7c5904206db504ea018d95d45", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "manera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "way,  manner"}, {"version": "1", "index": 22, "hash": "d79695776a5b40f7cadbee1f91a85c82", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fin", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 23, "hash": "401281b092fd5f950813ba41a39cee7d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tipo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "type,  kind"}, {"version": "1", "index": 24, "hash": "f146750e9027c272ca3213a49800255d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "people"}, {"version": "1", "index": 25, "hash": "2f1767dc31e7a8dc68b2c21bf07984ff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ejemplo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "example"}, {"version": "1", "index": 26, "hash": "21b12a2e1f594ee2d038e301fb7c2ca1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "side"}, {"version": "1", "index": 27, "hash": "31b397e3088041cb7da5138f51979d75", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hijo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "son,  [pl] children"}, {"version": "1", "index": 28, "hash": "a6fbce5746bb096dbf349062ca7f1f75", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "problema", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "problem"}, {"version": "1", "index": 29, "hash": "2ed75e258053b3abf12255476852a709", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuenta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bill,  account"}, {"version": "1", "index": 30, "hash": "71954c968ae9c3a50488ef0c9eae6f52", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "medio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "means,  middle; pormedio: through"}, {"version": "1", "index": 31, "hash": "d585c75f67ab4327ae31b88879f6e7c6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "palabra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "word"}, {"version": "1", "index": 32, "hash": "66e2d69fe0ec7dd2a6fd547b2e269303", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ni\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "child,  little boy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 33, "hash": "389cf996c10a51586fe27fd7a7e01ae2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sin embargo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "nevertheless"}, {"version": "1", "index": 34, "hash": "41409f34ee49036ad153fa10b374747e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "padre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "father"}, {"version": "1", "index": 35, "hash": "c65aea2c82a552d83ef8f02d8845ab2d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cambio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "change"}, {"version": "1", "index": 36, "hash": "7967791d08c33bfa3caa5e521b7957bb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "historia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "history,  story"}, {"version": "1", "index": 37, "hash": "1cba77c39b4d0a81024a7aada3655a28", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "idea", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "idea"}, {"version": "1", "index": 38, "hash": "edbce914409ab6a733e2e527fbe4349b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "agua", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "water"}, {"version": "1", "index": 39, "hash": "a60142eaf28c77df8aba656a0570b156", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "noche", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "night,  evening"}, {"version": "1", "index": 40, "hash": "f0c1a84f7910ef4eec9dcd5d22b5cd57", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ciudad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "city"}, {"version": "1", "index": 41, "hash": "b4bd3c0453ef20e66f2fcc026e3816ec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "modo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "way,  manner"}, {"version": "1", "index": 42, "hash": "7a675883b1c117e267470dce52eba518", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nombre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "name,  noun"}, {"version": "1", "index": 43, "hash": "2a9480c6a9d2fac0dfaddbc42632af67", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "familia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "family"}, {"version": "1", "index": 44, "hash": "bfb0c699e780f1a02464de4eb2d3b235", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "realidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reality,  actuality"}, {"version": "1", "index": 45, "hash": "aca14ddb3b72a1239301118ccd05f1ab", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "obra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "work,  book,  deed"}, {"version": "1", "index": 46, "hash": "19644c5336fa5fc4307a7d4f5b53d04a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "verdad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "truth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 47, "hash": "d2db8a610f8c7c0785d2d92a6e8c450e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mes", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "month"}, {"version": "1", "index": 48, "hash": "cd0a0b2fa8d815fce28b94e957f9dfe1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "raz\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reason; tener raz\u00f3n: to be right"}, {"version": "1", "index": 49, "hash": "9fbe2661c5e16cb142faed9abda2a806", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "grupo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "group"}, {"version": "1", "index": 50, "hash": "feda6365a6f6d14e799f3a8cd6d209c5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "relaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "relationship,  relation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 51, "hash": "10a27e92e358a19f43137acee70d54b9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuerpo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "body"}, {"version": "1", "index": 52, "hash": "f0002d2c3511209aa744e9121ec20ea5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hecho", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fact,  happening"}, {"version": "1", "index": 53, "hash": "71d4fa138503bfeee7b0bb8ac91e2cc0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "principio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "beginning,  principle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 54, "hash": "528059d6e5084feff6cbb1d11dbb19ee", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "se\u00f1or", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sir,  Mr,  lord"}, {"version": "1", "index": 55, "hash": "6d630f083461ea33b45e59e3398a1a72", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pueblo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "people,  village"}, {"version": "1", "index": 56, "hash": "8f6474354b496e66e8efde6c9576d69e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tarde", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "afternoon,  evening"}, {"version": "1", "index": 57, "hash": "dfe75bd98c8d113650e101c33fe1a93c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ojo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "eye"}, {"version": "1", "index": 58, "hash": "a458b917c78b16117f69ad142aae2040", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "calle", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "street"}, {"version": "1", "index": 59, "hash": "740f012345d61ecd008e19690ec193b7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "libro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "book"}, {"version": "1", "index": 60, "hash": "1fa0eaa2cc292458ac8b13e869e887e7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fuerza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "strength,  force,  power"}, {"version": "1", "index": 61, "hash": "4a45763fb8832658b8cfdf27bba1bd77", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "luz", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "light"}, {"version": "1", "index": 62, "hash": "ea07ff4e27d0bcf5f786f39e44e031f1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "santo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "saint (m)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 63, "hash": "007e610c52285521c4ec03fae05ce2e2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "frente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "al frente facing; frente a: across from"}, {"version": "1", "index": 64, "hash": "d94729ce13f4ee6395bfc6f1080cc986", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "amigo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "friend"}, {"version": "1", "index": 65, "hash": "2f2af81776721483feb9bb8f508f7962", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sentido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sense,  feeling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 66, "hash": "64b6ad10345af346e3733c868ac89012", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "paso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "step,  pace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 67, "hash": "3dc3584f0589558d2f05586959e464a6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "situaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "situation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 68, "hash": "703eb6d4af713d165435868a79518350", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gracia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(pl) thank you; grace,  favor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 69, "hash": "d0faa8334360c9755ea88766da46da44", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "siglo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "century,  age"}, {"version": "1", "index": 70, "hash": "a6923f6e2917066b987ebe0061018f22", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dios", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "God,  divinity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 71, "hash": "d5d9e9a9c63ab89aedc2364e35101be9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tierra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "earth,  land,  ground"}, {"version": "1", "index": 72, "hash": "acbf61dc603a375f7841d5bfd5ca928f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "papel", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "paper,  role,  part"}, {"version": "1", "index": 73, "hash": "2309f522cab926b42f4463fc656bd87f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "madre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mother"}, {"version": "1", "index": 74, "hash": "c5f3de31f3a2c4018f39966fa6563659", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tema", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "theme,  subject,  topic"}, {"version": "1", "index": 75, "hash": "a788e21b2906dfdac17a8792dcd6fae2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "clase", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "kind,  class,  order"}, {"version": "1", "index": 76, "hash": "c02138b94508ec621890a1f0899c1678", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dinero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "money"}, {"version": "1", "index": 77, "hash": "ddde8ff8c6e8fd414ff859cc85931461", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "campo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "field,  country"}, {"version": "1", "index": 78, "hash": "45963e6c73f5a13dbdee4ff92617c31b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cabeza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "head (part of body)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 79, "hash": "0c48401ed2ed2f3d1b3b9f1bb59cbc74", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "orden", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "order; sequence (m),  religious (f)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 80, "hash": "6a01bfa30172639e770a6aacb78a3ed4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "don", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "courtesy title (m),  Mr.,  gift"}, {"version": "1", "index": 81, "hash": "a897bd64ddf95b769c9024ab63fd45f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "semana", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "week"}, {"version": "1", "index": 82, "hash": "2a1585a864d9e67627c6ae04c807a2c5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "final", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "al final: finally,  in the end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 83, "hash": "6b1db9eac018b3d7379de76fcf968f7e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "inter\u00e9s", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "interest"}, {"version": "1", "index": 84, "hash": "a6460deaf1ed731e0389556d7ca9e662", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "view,  sight"}, {"version": "1", "index": 85, "hash": "ae98cb4b1401ff5abb53add0d325f93d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "acuerdo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "accord; de acuerdo: in agreement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 86, "hash": "9441fcf2c58eb467acdc177087f5fb15", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "n\u00famero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "number"}, {"version": "1", "index": 87, "hash": "e30d1b8e66df89e8e026f1147c03c691", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fondo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bottom,  end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 88, "hash": "95f72e4740fb033b2b4b32614cbe8224", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "camino", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "road,  route,  path"}, {"version": "1", "index": 89, "hash": "430c414abb7dfde3a92b85833b0c9973", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "voz", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "voice"}, {"version": "1", "index": 90, "hash": "01c8530da28619dce6d8a145bb3c444f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estudio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "study,  learning"}, {"version": "1", "index": 91, "hash": "01773a8a11c5f7314901bdae5825a190", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "valor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "value,  worth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 92, "hash": "151dc69112bfcb7d49b2721817a62ba5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "medida", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "measure; a medida que: to the extent"}, {"version": "1", "index": 93, "hash": "9484c73d200423b79f02cf29d55aedb7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "centro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "center,  middle,  downtown"}, {"version": "1", "index": 94, "hash": "c2705d2c26ed394e2df3470a128a3d2f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "necesidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "necessity,  need"}, {"version": "1", "index": 95, "hash": "aa3dd99b0439458d967fb9058ef68df7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "condici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "condition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 96, "hash": "b1207b95b13116469b29ef83963ee0ab", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "falta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lack,  shortage"}, {"version": "1", "index": 97, "hash": "a25dc04eb38a8cc2161e3d356fb9e9f5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "edad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "age"}, {"version": "1", "index": 98, "hash": "3b070dcca931ef68a6c64b12968ac505", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "state,  condition,  status"}, {"version": "1", "index": 99, "hash": "9df1c16e82351bd6abc74d230391cd1e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ser", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "being"}, {"version": "1", "index": 100, "hash": "5d4776149fde6b6d8ac75017a8dfef6e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "puerta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "door"}, {"version": "1", "index": 101, "hash": "ede319075e241e7b4be81bef28eef0fc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cara", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "face,  expression"}, {"version": "1", "index": 102, "hash": "aee1afd108b7cdf7983aa2e5cfc04198", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00e9poca", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "time,  age,  period"}, {"version": "1", "index": 103, "hash": "70dda5dfb8053dc6d1c492574bce9bfd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "color", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "color"}, {"version": "1", "index": 104, "hash": "e6050b5c0d2d08a29afe4861706071a0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "experiencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "experience"}, {"version": "1", "index": 105, "hash": "c5fe0408555dbf392918c6f77a4d01b2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "movimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "movement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 106, "hash": "5229e93d842db4f1103524ccad5f1f51", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pesar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sorrow; a pesar de: in spite of"}, {"version": "1", "index": 107, "hash": "84c729f675a47105374cd8c484b0371c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "posibilidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "possibility"}, {"version": "1", "index": 108, "hash": "1a98fcbc13d1350359b2a41ff02f9281", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "juego", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "game,  play,  sport"}, {"version": "1", "index": 109, "hash": "480ff51bbedd663cc813d8fb5dbc4490", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aire", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "air,  wind,  appearance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 110, "hash": "789a98094d69826637ffdef7ba575fee", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "guerra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "war,  warfare"}, {"version": "1", "index": 111, "hash": "c3a217d3df9d1f7ebea12fbb00f3a0a0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "resultado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "result,  outcome"}, {"version": "1", "index": 112, "hash": "3f85f188a71b745a89806eec337d34ea", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ley", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "law,  bill,  rule"}, {"version": "1", "index": 113, "hash": "f58ec3109099232109f08c2880bb079d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aspecto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "aspect,  appearance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 114, "hash": "ea702ba4205cb37a88cc84851690a7a5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pie", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "foot,  base"}, {"version": "1", "index": 115, "hash": "f67641788589421a7d9107857b0b7559", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "especie", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "kind,  sort,  species"}, {"version": "1", "index": 116, "hash": "842b1c521c6fdd195f85419d3d08db7b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "servicio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "service,  helpfulness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 117, "hash": "410cb0d3a7baa6d19232b688e1d28f46", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "actividad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "activity,  action"}, {"version": "1", "index": 118, "hash": "ca30965fc22c8736604e2ed6119b9635", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuesti\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "question,  matter"}, {"version": "1", "index": 119, "hash": "0596029a1c72f9e9e6b13ec66157fd54", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "duda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "doubt"}, {"version": "1", "index": 120, "hash": "024ab2d47053e543a7e53edb39b597a9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "diferencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "difference"}, {"version": "1", "index": 121, "hash": "4cc7f9871f26484152cbb7268d185c9c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ma\u00f1ana", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "morning,  tomorrow"}, {"version": "1", "index": 122, "hash": "96a081d6dc0c879673d52cb87765d3e1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cantidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "quantity,  amount"}, {"version": "1", "index": 123, "hash": "ebbe12dbbddb4d212b659e0d6df3c1ee", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "acci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "action,  act,  deed"}, {"version": "1", "index": 124, "hash": "8becbbf3f4ccd12e7c2a8bebdf56fd26", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sociedad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "society"}, {"version": "1", "index": 125, "hash": "e69136146f965d5bd81331f9234dfb01", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "peso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "peso (money),  weight,  load"}, {"version": "1", "index": 126, "hash": "3fd2e76ff09862c014fd28ae3c1b48ca", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "efecto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "effect"}, {"version": "1", "index": 127, "hash": "a8ea8a1aa42caa54430df153498515c6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "objeto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "object,  thing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 128, "hash": "5da2297bad6924526e48e00dbfc3c27a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "amor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "love"}, {"version": "1", "index": 129, "hash": "a1638a28a9603aafffaacabac1b79bdd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "muerte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "death"}, {"version": "1", "index": 130, "hash": "7c6121b0ff3ca245d9babbfb05e99a92", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "partido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "party,  group,  (sports) match"}, {"version": "1", "index": 131, "hash": "dcb201b195282662b8b152c9a5196f39", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "derecho", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "right,  justice,  law"}, {"version": "1", "index": 132, "hash": "6a065a3b0f83da435a7e1f5b7c7c107e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poder", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "power"}, {"version": "1", "index": 133, "hash": "2a8be3bfbcd491a36cc075319949b865", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "importancia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "importance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 134, "hash": "4c91d222b139eeccd6eb342f512ec180", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sistema", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "system"}, {"version": "1", "index": 135, "hash": "0408da5eadf5fd8327a2004b6ce574c2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "viaje", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "travel,  trip"}, {"version": "1", "index": 136, "hash": "3fb261d6446cc8e28dd04527b782b7ce", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "suelo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "ground,  floor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 137, "hash": "cae6f812183886f0f299ba00cc98e77f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "respecto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "respect,  con respecto a: with regards to"}, {"version": "1", "index": 138, "hash": "466c60cc4fc289b793c2b454ccfe393b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conocimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "knowledge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 139, "hash": "f0ab3f8e54e813ad8410d40f7cd4621c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "libertad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "freedom,  liberty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 140, "hash": "934d8a875151eb894f9ce84a442db497", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "atenci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "attention"}, {"version": "1", "index": 141, "hash": "690f326221661f4c2e7594a09f89917a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esfuerzo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "effort,  endeavor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 142, "hash": "9c6350b0aa51300d30790de1192fbcf8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "resto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "rest,  remainder,  leftover"}, {"version": "1", "index": 143, "hash": "c59b756920368254c670e9f464ba54f6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "zona", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "area,  zone"}, {"version": "1", "index": 144, "hash": "a830de01ef816594c0e133ff2edde596", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "miedo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fear"}, {"version": "1", "index": 145, "hash": "51dc26366d99bb5fa29cea4747565fec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "proceso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "process,  procedure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 146, "hash": "c04d94cfa036529812da2a3a9dffc408", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "minuto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "minute"}, {"version": "1", "index": 147, "hash": "85770ae9def3473f559e0dbe0609060a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mesa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "table,  board"}, {"version": "1", "index": 148, "hash": "3ef774a60e36f33ef6698f92d32a1fb1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ocasi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "opportunity,  occasion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 149, "hash": "5f280ec383b4ba88308dd92f3ac27250", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "programa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "program,  plan"}, {"version": "1", "index": 150, "hash": "047fb90408a79f189d51cbcea168b1a5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "favor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "favor,  benefit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 151, "hash": "dfba171a2beb6f4ec3bdf8c704e45032", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "respuesta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "answer,  reply"}, {"version": "1", "index": 152, "hash": "501b15162e15eb835f0a7eb8cd3abe89", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "l\u00ednea", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "line,  course"}, {"version": "1", "index": 153, "hash": "91736f96a46ba5a8a9d076bd18fb3377", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "espacio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "space,  room"}, {"version": "1", "index": 154, "hash": "d567c9b2d95fbc0a51e94d665abe9da3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nivel", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "level"}, {"version": "1", "index": 155, "hash": "91b4f42a84e88081dccb038aef11cfda", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gobierno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "government"}, {"version": "1", "index": 156, "hash": "476b57ddb0c4cb8101727206ce3dcc30", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cabo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "end,  bit; llevar a cabo: to carry out"}, {"version": "1", "index": 157, "hash": "d657fca3f2920c6c8c5d11f198cb7ef6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pregunta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "question"}, {"version": "1", "index": 158, "hash": "8c373fd1a64c1a3083fff348caf4b4ab", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "imagen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "image,  picture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 159, "hash": "b6397361d33457ec403604122074d886", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "carrera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "career,  course,  race"}, {"version": "1", "index": 160, "hash": "bd37cbbefac8c3499bf1ed2df830e4b8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "figura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "figure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 161, "hash": "1e4483e833025ac10e6184e75cb2d19d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "animal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "animal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 162, "hash": "593616de15330c0fb2d55e55410bf994", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "base", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "base,  basis"}, {"version": "1", "index": 163, "hash": "5aef6170d6d71c16bf951e4d178e759c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "posici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "position"}, {"version": "1", "index": 164, "hash": "22be503d9d0f7b4d64363930462297cb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "motivo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "motive,  cause"}, {"version": "1", "index": 165, "hash": "c893bad68927b457dbed39460e6afd62", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "prueba", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "proof,  trial,  test"}, {"version": "1", "index": 166, "hash": "54331b4b05717e224ca518ce938d80d6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pol\u00edtica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "politics,  policy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 167, "hash": "a7dec2eaa38d589b8f5ca3b6a4f01977", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "data,  fact"}, {"version": "1", "index": 168, "hash": "04299e213f5391ede16784de41dd847d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "empresa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "firm,  company,  venture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 169, "hash": "2cecbcbf404f2f22d1c232dcf450b56f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "asunto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "matter,  issue,  affair"}, {"version": "1", "index": 170, "hash": "ca24ec8700c914485a1055736abab81d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "presencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "presence,  appearance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 171, "hash": "e6da8e51b4510f9c253957d20dfd3090", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cultura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "culture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 172, "hash": "f263d9a8b7cb4a9e573c18e5b9e15091", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "serie", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "series"}, {"version": "1", "index": 173, "hash": "6aa15a9e3bccb2ef66e1555345636ffa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "car\u00e1cter", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "personality,  nature"}, {"version": "1", "index": 174, "hash": "cd83e72f7bc3e135a462f6fb0617c7ba", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mayor\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "majority"}, {"version": "1", "index": 175, "hash": "de57c5aeab2f35cee809fe5d00272fe9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escuela", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "school"}, {"version": "1", "index": 176, "hash": "7a25cefdc710b155828e91df70fe7478", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "autor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "writer,  author"}, {"version": "1", "index": 177, "hash": "330b3f0d763c562932754b1d835b3c2b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hermano", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "brother,  p siblings"}, {"version": "1", "index": 178, "hash": "d85029a2dcf2fd7e47bcab03fd350260", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "funci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "function,  meeting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 179, "hash": "b36a035d99171a31b4170bb6bd3176fa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "causa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cause"}, {"version": "1", "index": 180, "hash": "ed9023444507eb02fc69e3bb15a96aee", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "decisi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "decision"}, {"version": "1", "index": 181, "hash": "9ffea0730342a1d18b55906b192b0e81", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "m\u00fasica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "music"}, {"version": "1", "index": 182, "hash": "4e7176da26445378b203a89070ddfa9f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "expresi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "expression"}, {"version": "1", "index": 183, "hash": "8c7024f9223e216f4b9c2f32d75ba9b3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "r\u00edo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "river"}, {"version": "1", "index": 184, "hash": "8816314202d8fd95c8d2a91d829c12fb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "seguridad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "security,  safety"}, {"version": "1", "index": 185, "hash": "1a44be136a037ea58567f8d9d8647192", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "t\u00e9rmino", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "term (language),  end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 186, "hash": "b79d2096c66248cad58c309283bcd8d4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "metro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "meter,  subway"}, {"version": "1", "index": 187, "hash": "406c08e68877c23f13e583bde644fa6a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "m\u00e9dico", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "doctor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 188, "hash": "c8581bc43486c23ee099afe031f4de31", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "arte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "art,  skill"}, {"version": "1", "index": 189, "hash": "77a7c964abaa8ed78ed709b0904de2f3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "consecuencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "consequence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 190, "hash": "89ba4b3a2b02cdb3016633631a645c55", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "acto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "act,  action"}, {"version": "1", "index": 191, "hash": "27e110c11bce41980c004533253cdc78", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pena", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "trouble; valer la pena: be of worth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 192, "hash": "2b7b10774e36faa3a432def8887429b4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "segundo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "second"}, {"version": "1", "index": 193, "hash": "2c9890f44b5c56e6ce4bd86e993b5eaa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "altura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "height,  altitude"}, {"version": "1", "index": 194, "hash": "c06593d4d755428adc8a037e7104942b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "deseo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "desire,  wish"}, {"version": "1", "index": 195, "hash": "23eb064626d9953f79b24368d0839324", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "joven", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "teenager,  young person"}, {"version": "1", "index": 196, "hash": "3fb12df0659d42fa9e95ad2c442cccd7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sue\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dream,  sleep"}, {"version": "1", "index": 197, "hash": "5f59e63e21ec03a700a3f4fcd4c10120", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tarea", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "task,  job"}, {"version": "1", "index": 198, "hash": "a641ff223cb869fbfb74837f949e54a7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "carta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "letter,  (playing) card"}, {"version": "1", "index": 199, "hash": "5d53a7b888a9a175d79b500336208ec2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "propiedad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "property"}, {"version": "1", "index": 200, "hash": "286e18ee6617beaf7cfd0cb74b4b7824", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "producto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "product"}, {"version": "1", "index": 201, "hash": "66281aa9c8d17fdf7c1a4aa42f806508", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gusto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pleasure,  taste,  preference"}, {"version": "1", "index": 202, "hash": "fb4d0c4bc7fa4752016620069bf0970c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ayuda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "help,  aid"}, {"version": "1", "index": 203, "hash": "6cd7d1c43fcefc2031c6ad4e9c73ca33", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lengua", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "language,  tongue,  strip (of land)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 204, "hash": "5fc25157650d0cb24f02216d904584df", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "plan", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "plan"}, {"version": "1", "index": 205, "hash": "ca0e2e9b20a32f43e34b4f72cd366608", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vuelta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "return,  turn"}, {"version": "1", "index": 206, "hash": "7b6581ee30595c57d61332654cf30b0b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "proyecto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "project,  plan"}, {"version": "1", "index": 207, "hash": "9db9fafc83335335754a15461fe831cf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "memoria", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "memory"}, {"version": "1", "index": 208, "hash": "80e0d8d085a1120a47508a62e93b0f8e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "origen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "origin,  cause"}, {"version": "1", "index": 209, "hash": "af07e46299656b47b88f1164e50eacb5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "elemento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "element"}, {"version": "1", "index": 210, "hash": "5bd053a2e3d78b78f59fc9f05930d6a3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mercado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "market"}, {"version": "1", "index": 211, "hash": "1042013feadea5404c396dc5b7eb62ed", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "curso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "course,  direction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 212, "hash": "cc5bd058b77a20223dbcdce48eb8e19c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sangre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "blood"}, {"version": "1", "index": 213, "hash": "b79de4fb00edbedc3a2e300603b2be38", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "interior", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "interior,  inside"}, {"version": "1", "index": 214, "hash": "0f632877b7d9285c2182b346eae11835", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "uso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "use"}, {"version": "1", "index": 215, "hash": "d4276a6b733faa728ad04f2b0b7ea6e0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "brazo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "arm"}, {"version": "1", "index": 216, "hash": "793741d54b00253006453742ad4ed534", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "profesor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "professor,  teacher"}, {"version": "1", "index": 217, "hash": "5c72b79ee66109770d5813eb17112c12", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "futuro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "future"}, {"version": "1", "index": 218, "hash": "962aca2989c1d06bd59c2a084800e274", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "oportunidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "opportunity,  chance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 219, "hash": "7d30ff8fbb760664d263b0dc7cac42f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mitad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "half,  middle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 220, "hash": "bd8d4de401adec084befcad0a198298f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "recuerdo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "memory,  keepsake"}, {"version": "1", "index": 221, "hash": "9b880deb28dea6e84624498d364cb87f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "opini\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "opinion,  view"}, {"version": "1", "index": 222, "hash": "38c6c9fb8e6b578492864276921d37e3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "boca", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mouth,  entrance,  opening"}, {"version": "1", "index": 223, "hash": "9daab13bd0e9caf6d7ea2afbb8362e3f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "direcci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "direction,  address"}, {"version": "1", "index": 224, "hash": "165b816ccedeb0ff42d03fa894ad6028", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pieza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "piece,  part"}, {"version": "1", "index": 225, "hash": "02d4497aea62d795c2801c1e84916a70", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "actitud", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "attitude"}, {"version": "1", "index": 226, "hash": "5fa9db2e335ef69a4eeb9fe7974d61f4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sea"}, {"version": "1", "index": 227, "hash": "693fc3ac2e5be92d2b6bde862b5ac988", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "entrada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "entrance,  admisi\u00f3n ticket"}, {"version": "1", "index": 228, "hash": "0d87b5c76b4c480a107b621cc67f469d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "contacto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "contact"}, {"version": "1", "index": 229, "hash": "0ec846e8944bec2167597937cfa27cd0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "coraz\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "heart,  core"}, {"version": "1", "index": 230, "hash": "27f08504c8e23c89383aa5ad890892e9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "capital", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "capital; city (f),  money (m)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 231, "hash": "577d7ffba11e16282d12f8e874448c1a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "t\u00edtulo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "title,  heading"}, {"version": "1", "index": 232, "hash": "a0a864b5c5a316766debaa3721e3a683", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuarto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "room,  chamber"}, {"version": "1", "index": 233, "hash": "eec34d804c9ce6c89cff596be555e6a4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "material", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "material,  element"}, {"version": "1", "index": 234, "hash": "4d84b80853d3e0c81bc6dc4f03af893f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "golpe", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hit,  strike,  punch"}, {"version": "1", "index": 235, "hash": "84aa74a27dbb0630b1aefb8a3dc7aaf9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comunicaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "communication"}, {"version": "1", "index": 236, "hash": "b0b26828a73d30a10c82d236b0ed19f1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "enfermedad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "illness,  sickness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 237, "hash": "67d6c28fac7541d9ce1f46ba4f84e149", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "bien", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "goods,  property,  benefit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 238, "hash": "ea9f44d47a98e4434fe1ad9105c0c64a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "materia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "matter,  subject"}, {"version": "1", "index": 239, "hash": "694ddb80642c315591b3c0c2bb2f62f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sitio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "place,  space"}, {"version": "1", "index": 240, "hash": "65ff09ac85bd02a94a3b1f43296ed004", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "naturaleza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "nature,  character"}, {"version": "1", "index": 241, "hash": "f6a4bdd3a66fc668ae2a9d25ccddee2f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "capacidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "capacity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 242, "hash": "7f28a31a04429c370a5232d51b77a3df", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "distancia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "distance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 243, "hash": "e7c033f1077176f5b24c31f231f80721", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "informaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "information"}, {"version": "1", "index": 244, "hash": "0149c3083ec080ee00b622bd2495525d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ambiente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "environment,  atmosphere"}, {"version": "1", "index": 245, "hash": "acbf157754bc921e70ab30b1e79c75f5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "desarrollo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "development"}, {"version": "1", "index": 246, "hash": "12313a3d28f802e3a22b07d2e01c6dcf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sol", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sun"}, {"version": "1", "index": 247, "hash": "864659e2d490712c9ea0e1c27214c7fa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "compa\u00f1ero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "companion,  classmate"}, {"version": "1", "index": 248, "hash": "5c894636500f788f3cd2d513b1050679", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "salida", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "exit,  escape,  outcome"}, {"version": "1", "index": 249, "hash": "3f66a5c20b33faff460b0478569943e3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conciencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "conscience,  consciousness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 250, "hash": "4b86640d50f19cb8c36215a8b600ae6a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "costumbre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "habit,  custom,  usage"}, {"version": "1", "index": 251, "hash": "e003268a052a053ee5ec481e2a097648", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "paz", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "peace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 252, "hash": "d449581e7fcff1855fe50fcf15caff19", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "noticia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "news"}, {"version": "1", "index": 253, "hash": "0f23314ee86abdeba09da52effb368f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "circunstancia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "circumstance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 254, "hash": "a98931d104a7fb8f30450547d97e7ca5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dolor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pain,  ache,  sorrow"}, {"version": "1", "index": 255, "hash": "28abf1d6d9f00154628bdf2ddb740b3f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estilo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "style"}, {"version": "1", "index": 256, "hash": "b26dd018cac0dd997ba96451c63445bc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "precio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "price,  cost,  value"}, {"version": "1", "index": 257, "hash": "c49ad902e79879c9acd5da3920d5e448", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "planta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "plant,  floor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 258, "hash": "56de844e3a04d7f05dc0fbb46d4dcc61", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "personaje", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "character (e.g. movie)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 259, "hash": "6dd5e1294c2ef993bc611fd8c17370fc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00e9xito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "success"}, {"version": "1", "index": 260, "hash": "48f806dcb212cd60ea55243edf449463", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hija", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "daughter"}, {"version": "1", "index": 261, "hash": "767e864c02f6e856f2e0804d95165853", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "edificio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "building"}, {"version": "1", "index": 262, "hash": "9cd3ded95926f23db1d6591be2141a77", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "autoridad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "authority"}, {"version": "1", "index": 263, "hash": "645d267aa931167c17f0e43714093ea2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "piedra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "stone,  rock"}, {"version": "1", "index": 264, "hash": "3c58b0ccb6386b263789e7d9939e6076", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conjunto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "group,  set"}, {"version": "1", "index": 265, "hash": "0ce6b516a0ca752c32b4c5e9f0bcf22c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "suerte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "luck,  fortune"}, {"version": "1", "index": 266, "hash": "3ec3dc60f2e6600b3287adac4aafe9bf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esp\u00edritu", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "spirit,  ghost"}, {"version": "1", "index": 267, "hash": "3c485c0fcde7ffc95cd4c1ab07d061b1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "miembro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "member,  limb"}, {"version": "1", "index": 268, "hash": "41fc38105c0e27507201dee05e1e2fde", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "recurso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "resource,  recourse,  means"}, {"version": "1", "index": 269, "hash": "608bbf2c6b1dc1e79809734bf699be52", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pared", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(interior) wall"}, {"version": "1", "index": 270, "hash": "3d80f3524650008035bea85725120ac1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "equipo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "team,  equipment,  outfit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 271, "hash": "cb5e100e5a9a3e7f6d1fd97512215282", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "error", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "error,  mistake"}, {"version": "1", "index": 272, "hash": "da774ad0ef5b732e0f66a001114e6079", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dificultad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "difficulty,  obstacle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 273, "hash": "70e7164e32565848c25fe5d706cbef52", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "voluntad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "will,  willpower,  intention"}, {"version": "1", "index": 274, "hash": "53edfd93a7c0c6bb2e7e44b2c433d22a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reuni\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "meeting,  reunion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 275, "hash": "72aaecacee08f7d2a4eca1ecac6a10cb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "modelo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "model,  pattern"}, {"version": "1", "index": 276, "hash": "94ed416723ce619a79d9bf5ecb292718", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fecha", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "date,  day"}, {"version": "1", "index": 277, "hash": "ebb499e59780839b2426c6d255695f66", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "prop\u00f3sito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "intention,  purpose"}, {"version": "1", "index": 278, "hash": "ac9004b56f9eb1490d6d5887aa2a2f3e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuidado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "care,  carefulness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 279, "hash": "4400c8954992db43f9c0adb421a44c9d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "puesto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "job,  place,  position"}, {"version": "1", "index": 280, "hash": "d6d85d89b4612501521435bd3f620a9a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "grado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "degree,  grade"}, {"version": "1", "index": 281, "hash": "3509e677541bf68da4a9e7244e9d4fb6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lucha", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fight,  struggle,  wrestle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 282, "hash": "8d6d3e8b969523e95759e85628aec9ce", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "jefe", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "leader,  boss,  manager"}, {"version": "1", "index": 283, "hash": "edd3c7409a1916ce3f42a7c9d8cd2329", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "peri\u00f3dico", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "newspaper,  periodical"}, {"version": "1", "index": 284, "hash": "d018268506e2868537a478629b59e7c1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "par", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pair,  couple (m); a la par: at same time"}, {"version": "1", "index": 285, "hash": "2bd3118bf83df1faebaf4ffa0b3014d1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "p\u00fablico", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "public,  audience"}, {"version": "1", "index": 286, "hash": "d8911124a43dbc68e306f7d1420fdb54", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "calidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "quality"}, {"version": "1", "index": 287, "hash": "50eeb5d6417b1687fd71bb3952a524db", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ciencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "science,  knowledge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 288, "hash": "c4660dc7fc1ea93a06036187ffd44720", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tama\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "size,  dimension"}, {"version": "1", "index": 289, "hash": "f9f16d97c90d8c6f2cab37bb6d1f1992", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "doctor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "doctor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 290, "hash": "0e6f85f8a301bed8b0773f679fa080fb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuadro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "painting,  picture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 291, "hash": "c4c688ad65096da11d3ef771116e05e4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caballo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "horse"}, {"version": "1", "index": 292, "hash": "3652d25792fbc7e847b2300df6af3127", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "responsabilidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "responsibility"}, {"version": "1", "index": 293, "hash": "f019564bfcfa0a562d25341e83ca087b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "detalle", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "detail"}, {"version": "1", "index": 294, "hash": "697542111b0c55793382eabdfce3f697", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "marcha", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "march,  progress"}, {"version": "1", "index": 295, "hash": "409f4cd5e6a103f5a0d4bfcc18215b0e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "carne", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "meat,  flesh"}, {"version": "1", "index": 296, "hash": "df7fb5614a6a303c044c26e1d303654c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pensamiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "thought,  thinking"}, {"version": "1", "index": 297, "hash": "f91cd5d61e1e331b360fdbfe56588cbf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cargo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "position,  charge,  fee"}, {"version": "1", "index": 298, "hash": "98809c3f491160651ce442f657c62218", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "santa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "saint (f)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 299, "hash": "c8a2c85dd26d7b04c0210f24172566ca", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "construcci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "construction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 300, "hash": "c94788fc00683c8a37e64ceddbd49a71", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "juicio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "judgment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 301, "hash": "34f20ce786ccecc1add518d67e8aca87", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "terreno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "ground,  earth,  terrain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 302, "hash": "309b1d8e870c6711d5731b0b26b695eb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "piso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "floor,  storey"}, {"version": "1", "index": 303, "hash": "b9ac50817fc948d806ccc6adc47fa9c9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "compa\u00f1\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "company"}, {"version": "1", "index": 304, "hash": "62059a74e9330e9dc2f537f712b8797c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "texto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "text"}, {"version": "1", "index": 305, "hash": "f4c42111465db6fd128f68dcfa970152", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fuente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "source; fountain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 306, "hash": "c0cbc0bd20dabae8cc946f893d6e7b41", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "presente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "present"}, {"version": "1", "index": 307, "hash": "61c060041a93525481b4c16c811fce51", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "revista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "magazine,  journal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 308, "hash": "6c5d50e7e28bf5b4319fa47c58e0483a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esperanza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hope"}, {"version": "1", "index": 309, "hash": "58fff93447c5aa1d264b5384719949c5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "m\u00e1quina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "machine"}, {"version": "1", "index": 310, "hash": "18341ec4b96d60e29c5bf6bdbe42fdbb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "frase", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "phrase,  sentence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 311, "hash": "6b694e8cf87fc88d392ed8ebf81d9385", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sala", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "room,  hall"}, {"version": "1", "index": 312, "hash": "6e97fde6a5dbd67d16dac6847a553b0a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "instrumento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "instrument"}, {"version": "1", "index": 313, "hash": "c07155ef19245c8923deb2b276b7efef", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "defensa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "defense,  plea"}, {"version": "1", "index": 314, "hash": "3d4e992d8d8a7d848724aa26ed7f4176", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "director", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "director,  manager,  principal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 315, "hash": "3f02d0263b027dc8f099d1e74f78fa32", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "explicaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "explanation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 316, "hash": "264bf1589333e4571eee802618c51850", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "art\u00edculo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "article,  product,  item"}, {"version": "1", "index": 317, "hash": "a398fb77df76e6153df57cd65fd0a7c5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "radio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "radio; set (m),  communication (f)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 318, "hash": "3a05805db57d2ee1ff13dcbc56eefb01", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pel\u00edcula", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "movie,  film"}, {"version": "1", "index": 319, "hash": "6e6e83c7cbb799ab2b928c4dc01c76b6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "elecci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "election,  choice"}, {"version": "1", "index": 320, "hash": "d57aae6ea653fef4c22139fb28cff8a6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "visita", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "visit,  visitor,  guest"}, {"version": "1", "index": 321, "hash": "c033ff7f8bc45d436207ffe8068e3784", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "apoyo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "support,  backing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 322, "hash": "1c4708df8cb006d2a007b3920a7b92a5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "presidente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "president"}, {"version": "1", "index": 323, "hash": "ffce3759c0d736c5365efe989eb2e16e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "arma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "weapon"}, {"version": "1", "index": 324, "hash": "ff3eb1a68dde833cc0ad87902579d31f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00e1rbol", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tree"}, {"version": "1", "index": 325, "hash": "43cfb337f8901990787ec7c8c76e6791", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "encuentro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "meeting,  game,  skirmish"}, {"version": "1", "index": 326, "hash": "0c47a816148277d6d8a181a1543f49f3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "corriente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "current,  flow"}, {"version": "1", "index": 327, "hash": "80f1f8acac48f32c5f9b918bc14afdca", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lectura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reading"}, {"version": "1", "index": 328, "hash": "4429fcef6a577367be5e19e7f07087f4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "existencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "existence,  life"}, {"version": "1", "index": 329, "hash": "b543cef422de90ddf286c6292a66ed44", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lenguaje", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "language,  speech"}, {"version": "1", "index": 330, "hash": "ce604407b420b7de3df81516e16a09cc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "destino", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "destination,  destiny"}, {"version": "1", "index": 331, "hash": "ddb86667ae018a3a5e9e59d71b7adea4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "educaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "education"}, {"version": "1", "index": 332, "hash": "8aa6d4933db0d53d436ee048d1b9cdd3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "operaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "operation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 333, "hash": "1d72002615a6e1914d45c1078044d3bc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nota", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "note,  grade"}, {"version": "1", "index": 334, "hash": "4c16f83f480928bb12fc21f7fb0e85ec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "teatro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "theater,  drama"}, {"version": "1", "index": 335, "hash": "0d6e3a88f42f1eefa1d2a28e9102811c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "negocio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "business,  transaction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 336, "hash": "7e9cde7f9cb124af659827bc2e6aeb5b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "letra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "letter,  handwriting,  lyrics"}, {"version": "1", "index": 337, "hash": "be9811245bd57485cdcd30bded8e97e4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sentimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "feeling,  sentiment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 338, "hash": "6ac0b6b47e85e1cb0ce4efb7e8ee5558", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "soluci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "solution,  answer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 339, "hash": "c501b276ec5ccc53995004be2b15cb0d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comida", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "food,  meal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 340, "hash": "bcb5e9b44a16fd7e9e07687c303c9d71", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "impresi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "impression,  printing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 341, "hash": "2e6d2b03a0ad1e4359edd46b98c551d7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "plano", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "plane,  map,  level"}, {"version": "1", "index": 342, "hash": "cafd66fb7c05cd01fdfcbc15489e0497", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "intenci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "intention"}, {"version": "1", "index": 343, "hash": "4ec61f637a5e90f8fef5ec75334a3f3c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ritmo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "rhythm"}, {"version": "1", "index": 344, "hash": "4ab10179e578c4421552ab639aef64aa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "banco", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(financial) bank,  bench"}, {"version": "1", "index": 345, "hash": "137dbdecce7839d8ade2e680c482ca76", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "piel", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "skin,  hide,  fur"}, {"version": "1", "index": 346, "hash": "fc5364bf9dbfa34954526becad136d4b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "control", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "control"}, {"version": "1", "index": 347, "hash": "ab11106c5dc94551d4a3da1e9836c1d0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "investigaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "investigation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 348, "hash": "609251c4192dffa10959626e9424b271", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conversaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "conversation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 349, "hash": "23804201a61343a663a7a44afc3a2e5b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "verano", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "summer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 350, "hash": "2ad84b96238e23a765d116c5523c9a36", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "respeto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "respect,  regard"}, {"version": "1", "index": 351, "hash": "19e1be30823e244159fbbd51168fa0c4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "norte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "north"}, {"version": "1", "index": 352, "hash": "6d5e39c96b33919b0e1f94c346e965b3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tradici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tradition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 353, "hash": "f21b2c390af25c537b565acdb8145d04", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poblaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "population"}, {"version": "1", "index": 354, "hash": "2283064f6e2814fb780d95059d6eb273", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pareja", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "couple,  pair"}, {"version": "1", "index": 355, "hash": "0ba7622bc3d8e6943ce4716eb9f7cec9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pasado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "past"}, {"version": "1", "index": 356, "hash": "cb17f19a45e28539e5f1eae490bf222c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "diario", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "newspaper"}, {"version": "1", "index": 357, "hash": "40c961cd55d69f243ecfe9a0fdbcef7a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "generaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "generation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 358, "hash": "c7545945875174a977ae574d4fb0a31f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "visi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "vision"}, {"version": "1", "index": 359, "hash": "e1d1654e5e78245e2cd209bffa9a97a6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "peligro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "danger,  menace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 360, "hash": "a13314e5b7614acf77e65427af6d3791", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "oro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "gold vino wine"}, {"version": "1", "index": 361, "hash": "0e755887dc19b7938e22655dc73c8205", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "etapa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "stage,  period"}, {"version": "1", "index": 362, "hash": "d1dd1bba0213b4b960307b53046dce67", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "silencio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "silence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 363, "hash": "0335e2c3d9ca2e06e206cbf5ff8d7536", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "artista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "artist,  performer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 364, "hash": "d552cecbaf1a5a64066b42e5d25d282a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "labor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "labor,  work,  task"}, {"version": "1", "index": 365, "hash": "be7740aa9d6f946349d2a54c8d133160", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cielo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sky,  heaven,  ceiling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 366, "hash": "3d116163e002737ff4082b6778b9d32f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pr\u00e1ctica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "practice,  skill"}, {"version": "1", "index": 367, "hash": "355e8847aba7f288765356adc042684c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "l\u00edmite", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "limit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 368, "hash": "34733b1051f1f214b81e186cf9babc35", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "masa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mass,  dough,  bulk,  crowd"}, {"version": "1", "index": 369, "hash": "1505c287ce2fdc2ffae7b824d5ec9fb7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "formaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "formation,  education"}, {"version": "1", "index": 370, "hash": "d44b121fc3524fe5cdc4f3feb31ceb78", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "perro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dog"}, {"version": "1", "index": 371, "hash": "fbe6e17aeac52ebcdc5eac9ff64961be", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "izquierda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "left"}, {"version": "1", "index": 372, "hash": "dd50bcf3a0871aa7b1efd421267c90dc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "energ\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "energy,  power"}, {"version": "1", "index": 373, "hash": "99be2bf3fe45f15fc6b7f7715fc789b7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "confianza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "confidence,  trust"}, {"version": "1", "index": 374, "hash": "d38e99d9790733c939e88698afbc30b6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "flor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "flower"}, {"version": "1", "index": 375, "hash": "ef72f789cacaf7014033a6a654e0cd9b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esposa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wife"}, {"version": "1", "index": 376, "hash": "d1f08063a62b65c1b18ffd308e870c0c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "revoluci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "revolution"}, {"version": "1", "index": 377, "hash": "7a7ea6908e33896ddcc8b82f264f4f7a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "maestro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "teacher (m),  master"}, {"version": "1", "index": 378, "hash": "11f813666fb3bd871186d6429f4adbfc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fen\u00f3meno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "phenomenon"}, {"version": "1", "index": 379, "hash": "c7cebe523903e9ac59856c7cd2adf357", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "presi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pressure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 380, "hash": "c6865cf98b133f1f3de596a4a2894630", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alumno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "student,  pupil"}, {"version": "1", "index": 381, "hash": "cd44fae4d18636e890d693df389a3b3e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "teor\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "theory"}, {"version": "1", "index": 382, "hash": "14d2d4119982cd6c68a566e523cb16ae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tono", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tone"}, {"version": "1", "index": 383, "hash": "6776b3dd95bba354801deda2cb769122", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "salud", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "health"}, {"version": "1", "index": 384, "hash": "67dffea72acd1c6a3ccd43a6df8da612", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "se\u00f1ora", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "Mrs.,  lady,  madam"}, {"version": "1", "index": 385, "hash": "5755c7e4df669276165e86c6958370be", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "v\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "por v\u00eda: by means; road,  way"}, {"version": "1", "index": 386, "hash": "ebbc3c26a34b609dc46f5c3378f96e08", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "soul"}, {"version": "1", "index": 387, "hash": "2433f6a533fb465ef55f459b4a89c68a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "madera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wood"}, {"version": "1", "index": 388, "hash": "568db2702369c052e099e5f962fca452", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fiesta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "party,  feast"}, {"version": "1", "index": 389, "hash": "e5ce98be0cc9de99e35ebfe1ce6a8863", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "calor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "heat,  warmth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 390, "hash": "1d69f0b4a68cb5bde6ae2234c895eb8b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hogar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "home,  hearth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 391, "hash": "bbd5894942a8098703a5198dc4b71a36", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mind"}, {"version": "1", "index": 392, "hash": "8dfd9ffef138617eb73e4744bb7afde5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "preocupaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "worry,  concern"}, {"version": "1", "index": 393, "hash": "a1b7f3dd4c87736ced4cf18fce77a227", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "concepto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "concept"}, {"version": "1", "index": 394, "hash": "40e29c52b5dc2b1e45d8a30880f1cebc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tel\u00e9fono", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "phone,  telephone"}, {"version": "1", "index": 395, "hash": "5f01c0ceea38f3875e271db995e1d390", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hoja", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sheet,  leaf"}, {"version": "1", "index": 396, "hash": "ca963d9cc07e9f182f6d9d0adde67006", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escritor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "writer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 397, "hash": "f9295b4b31f6d699dccce2a4ef5014e1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "intento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "attempt,  try"}, {"version": "1", "index": 398, "hash": "4914eb8147a0c8e6a66d0d1774348931", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "regla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "rule,  ruler,  regulation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 399, "hash": "1f385231a3704957eb8b1d62050ccde4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "riesgo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "risk"}, {"version": "1", "index": 400, "hash": "516faa3fee62867efbe789d3c02a1b7a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "polic\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "police,  police force,  police officer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 401, "hash": "e4e4564027d73a4325024d948d167e93", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estudiante", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "student"}, {"version": "1", "index": 402, "hash": "92b32908e8b9f9b67d4fb5d580524a7f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "plaza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "square,  marketplace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 403, "hash": "eb8d3f1b179bfca7a3d31880b4d66778", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llamada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "call,  knock"}, {"version": "1", "index": 404, "hash": "b62003ddc1b76aa550ebe4532ddd3433", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sensaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sensation,  feeling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 405, "hash": "c612ed774b958419b12096bc1a8e6849", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "enemigo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "enemy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 406, "hash": "59d47b448a8b505d1c6413cc3ed95aff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "unidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "unit,  unity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 407, "hash": "70e3772cea46250e7cbb1b6125a3617c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "idioma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(specific) language"}, {"version": "1", "index": 408, "hash": "4a9ecaa64985d13f011943394ad60ac1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ra\u00edz", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "root"}, {"version": "1", "index": 409, "hash": "aa9354af6ab6844652e91bcd8659c464", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "compromiso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "compromise,  engagement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 410, "hash": "e417046f842cb9300ba6e760e0a0bc9e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comentario", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "remark,  comment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 411, "hash": "c85066aadf0d68d56074dcdb5c395656", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "carga", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "load,  charge,  cargo"}, {"version": "1", "index": 412, "hash": "01a9a0934c76691a10025b5dbad887ef", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "marido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "husband"}, {"version": "1", "index": 413, "hash": "012d1d0bdb0a189c94000d68067bd773", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "derecha", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "right,  right hand"}, {"version": "1", "index": 414, "hash": "c946d5c13b18d96e134eb3bf3146b25d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "extremo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "edge,  border,  end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 415, "hash": "5fb087abfbc77088535610dff30a88a2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "individuo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "individual,  person"}, {"version": "1", "index": 416, "hash": "57bb4b485f52628aab93cbde76d322d0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "contenido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "contents,  content"}, {"version": "1", "index": 417, "hash": "cf5e7118725cb9bf8b59f9a0367dfb57", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "obligaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "obligation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 418, "hash": "3a35b31c63faed7adea75909b0a853b6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "corte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "court (f),  cut (m)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 419, "hash": "fbb44b4487415b134bce9c790a27fe5e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "total", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(sum) total"}, {"version": "1", "index": 420, "hash": "0b8ccf516150247ab7c8855150c90602", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "da\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "harm,  injury,  damage"}, {"version": "1", "index": 421, "hash": "2652eee01d2620e9c5e55f6ac9d4b433", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mensaje", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "message"}, {"version": "1", "index": 422, "hash": "ecd2ec43c588ae012e3550fcc55d6009", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "list,  roster,  roll"}, {"version": "1", "index": 423, "hash": "d48d20cd5f26e1e15ab8ff806599496a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "regi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "region"}, {"version": "1", "index": 424, "hash": "b4030b09a4fd84600e92a6d0f560c062", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ni\u00f1a", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "child,  young girl"}, {"version": "1", "index": 425, "hash": "6a15b615e7eab8883637e54fb2977b01", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "culpa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "blame,  fault"}, {"version": "1", "index": 426, "hash": "5ae1e26539389e7097434f172a18e409", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "discusi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "discussion,  argument"}, {"version": "1", "index": 427, "hash": "c85075e023fdd49a8622982eafa2b5af", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pelo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hair"}, {"version": "1", "index": 428, "hash": "2d917f5d1275e96fd75e6352e26b1387", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fe", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "faith"}, {"version": "1", "index": 429, "hash": "ba8a9096beaed12fc808ad3bd85a43fd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "referencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reference,  allusion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 430, "hash": "a587b16e0a2c4a9c61feee6486c3a6c5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sur", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "south"}, {"version": "1", "index": 431, "hash": "3d2500700c281e6504b2b728dcf62a72", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gesto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "gesture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 432, "hash": "e50d6c715ad1383f1656172025445cf9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "perspectiva", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "perspective"}, {"version": "1", "index": 433, "hash": "5f3ba3e22380ac07214f7f2d8163d6ba", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "colegio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(high) school,  college"}, {"version": "1", "index": 434, "hash": "81d0d58d3b7e35bc6a6f3ad7fc5563af", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "venta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sale"}, {"version": "1", "index": 435, "hash": "34240997a16763c011134c570fcc149e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "documento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "document"}, {"version": "1", "index": 436, "hash": "fc5dce399714211cad0900db85510084", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "televisi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "TV,  television"}, {"version": "1", "index": 437, "hash": "56daf002d328229cf4ef837e0b0ecbde", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "chico", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "boy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 438, "hash": "e6768600e0920292695bb24bd6a4142b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "novela", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "novel"}, {"version": "1", "index": 439, "hash": "a8b0b6d9acecdb23f411f99e0c6ea2a0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alcance", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reach,  scope"}, {"version": "1", "index": 440, "hash": "93162408a498e22f9b15007a3eb4a31c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "crisis", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "crisis"}, {"version": "1", "index": 441, "hash": "9044d1926a8376e3d7201fbff013d3e3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "literatura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "literature"}, {"version": "1", "index": 442, "hash": "c3370b72a11f601a944fc7629317ebcd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "batalla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "battle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 443, "hash": "ec10b554dc4f5c290aba276c4c530446", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "due\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "owner,  landlord (m)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 444, "hash": "e1c06fd96d694b6236f635bf0281cf55", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vecino", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "neighbor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 445, "hash": "ce323b11b2e18fc9c1db1da870bacaa8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sector", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sector,  area,  section"}, {"version": "1", "index": 446, "hash": "01b74b3ff51fd424cdd58989dbf9c7ad", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pintura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "painting,  paint"}, {"version": "1", "index": 447, "hash": "12615a0b77c9e6456d39916bee9bbf51", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "accidente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "accident,  irregularity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 448, "hash": "26c21a4f44b8f9c47a5cc022bfa9484f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "influencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "influence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 449, "hash": "088ef99bff55c67dc863f83980a66a9b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "empleado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "employee"}, {"version": "1", "index": 450, "hash": "ae4654e72ae84b204814aa203e094100", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "moneda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "coins,  currency"}, {"version": "1", "index": 451, "hash": "07ce8e74a0ac9492c130c93b732d45de", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "facilidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "ease,  facility"}, {"version": "1", "index": 452, "hash": "ee6cdf304be4419412434a1389cae9ef", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "matrimonio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "marriage,  married couple"}, {"version": "1", "index": 453, "hash": "1b3f85340906e89525d0f0f3621accfa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "iglesia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "church"}, {"version": "1", "index": 454, "hash": "5995f7bf8009e3c6aa148ab78d62331b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "oficina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "office"}, {"version": "1", "index": 455, "hash": "fde7be821de11237ee88a413808b562c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "instituci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "institution"}, {"version": "1", "index": 456, "hash": "2c309f3d14b2aa114cc09dc0f4a33257", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fr\u00edo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cold"}, {"version": "1", "index": 457, "hash": "f642fa88a7d86bf07d64744c433e6354", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "domingo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "Sunday"}, {"version": "1", "index": 458, "hash": "f64c87919e462617c66ab46800fe5a07", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reacci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reaction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 459, "hash": "f9ee01ee4ed413fe1c926d2af09effad", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "acontecimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "event,  happening"}, {"version": "1", "index": 460, "hash": "2fe44044f40217387daaf299f2eb7340", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "costa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "coast"}, {"version": "1", "index": 461, "hash": "0f07d02867304bbc5cc02ebfdb180066", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "m\u00e9todo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "method"}, {"version": "1", "index": 462, "hash": "2920094be91df1ad2587792e4011a44e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comunidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "community"}, {"version": "1", "index": 463, "hash": "014f3ddbafc107dd392c438a449433cf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "coche", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "car,  carriage"}, {"version": "1", "index": 464, "hash": "6192fea33e5a79c36abb684172b88d66", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "p\u00e1gina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "page"}, {"version": "1", "index": 465, "hash": "458a8a1ed545f5b0d385c90849e3e7d8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "frecuencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "frequency"}, {"version": "1", "index": 466, "hash": "dd5a9baf3ff58d89b024c326f8dbbb49", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conclusi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "conclusion,  end"}, {"version": "1", "index": 467, "hash": "7b29fe9fab258d70394f9e54bbdeff90", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escena", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "scene,  stage,  setting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 468, "hash": "e1427d0dc032be74c732581a31aa8f75", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estructura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "structure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 469, "hash": "f80b7cd87c1a3a5d325ee2b39e78d18a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "beneficio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "benefit,  profit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 470, "hash": "32aec3de48d501622e3e5c75670924e5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alimento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "food,  nourishment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 471, "hash": "b9c47b546aacac3f78918264ad87309c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "velocidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "speed,  velocity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 472, "hash": "ef475799760ce4ade5903912a79cfe39", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "barrio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "neighborhood,  district"}, {"version": "1", "index": 473, "hash": "992c2cfee6d37bc263298a684d9b677e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "an\u00e1lisis", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "analysis"}, {"version": "1", "index": 474, "hash": "9c3591f1ea413a920a860bd134590762", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "frontera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "border,  frontier"}, {"version": "1", "index": 475, "hash": "a610ab17dd3d54a33990fcad83f04f16", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "temor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fear"}, {"version": "1", "index": 476, "hash": "59f5d0e34ae972f23e9a5e59f5ade66f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ataque", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "attack,  raid"}, {"version": "1", "index": 477, "hash": "23a1c740ff145d7962d469ec2153bf06", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cine", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cinema,  US movie theater"}, {"version": "1", "index": 478, "hash": "e04f28cc33cb20274dd3ff44e600a923", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rama", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "branch,  bough,  limb"}, {"version": "1", "index": 479, "hash": "185bce252b8343779be14fa451cc4bea", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comienzo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "start,  beginning"}, {"version": "1", "index": 480, "hash": "78ae959170be4ee86febe81df5ffe4df", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "barco", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "boat,  ship"}, {"version": "1", "index": 481, "hash": "3f0e3a5f97c69751068c09d4f21fb950", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "partida", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "game,  match,  departure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 482, "hash": "4bc1c163975e840fd5f0f4234642303b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aparato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "apparatus,  device"}, {"version": "1", "index": 483, "hash": "e229faf649f0a5b28ce2c7dc1b86300e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "extranjero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "foreigner"}, {"version": "1", "index": 484, "hash": "2f9d90b6b3de564745a49c4a1132e349", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "c\u00e1mara", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "camera,  chamber"}, {"version": "1", "index": 485, "hash": "07aea1ec662bcfdbf14a7a71734cc48a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "creaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "creation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 486, "hash": "57e6e9b3ce8603fde63fb396e2a57f83", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gana", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "desire"}, {"version": "1", "index": 487, "hash": "b19270709717161a079f38dcd667c81a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "moda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fashion,  form"}, {"version": "1", "index": 488, "hash": "0cc8bea8f407f1a2ea1ec0a0885bb39a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ruido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "noise"}, {"version": "1", "index": 489, "hash": "fc4b5e2c4b748868deb19d350c831f4d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cama", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bed (furniture)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 490, "hash": "0f844bc9d31ab09a4697de7115e26871", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "t\u00e9cnica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "technique,  skill"}, {"version": "1", "index": 491, "hash": "e0fac37e1d6e90a50a02184a1e09a884", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "consejo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "advice,  council,  counsel"}, {"version": "1", "index": 492, "hash": "6636dc2bc4fb99725ee10cf5eae20005", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "violencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "violence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 493, "hash": "22c6312f3079928a654de2e3291c0d0a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sonido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sound"}, {"version": "1", "index": 494, "hash": "aa87ddc5b4c24406d26ddad771ef44b0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estrella", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "star"}, {"version": "1", "index": 495, "hash": "9e0bc11db04186f2afcfa92e398bf437", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mirada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "gaze,  look"}, {"version": "1", "index": 496, "hash": "5db73634ccdaf36fa3168124ebfba592", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pierna", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "leg"}, {"version": "1", "index": 497, "hash": "dfe94c1b4bf7bdc2dc5bba511ee95688", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hambre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hunger,  starvation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 498, "hash": "379b7307cb7b05c9ca0c2edc727bc866", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "placer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pleasure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 499, "hash": "341db4aced60f1fb1831bbbebcb98c35", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "profesi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "profession,  occupation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 500, "hash": "a75c2428115553f5a297a5fec636c6ae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "objetivo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "objective"}, {"version": "1", "index": 501, "hash": "b2f39f17253fa5e90a05d637249c53e1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "honor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "honor,  honesty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 502, "hash": "ef445f636e90112ba4151228d6d18d1e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "monta\u00f1a", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mountain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 503, "hash": "d3bd99c828e265e7448a16155e6b84d5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "instante", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "instant,  moment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 504, "hash": "e6ca928d4e3b7547c68ed61af139d5aa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "viento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wind,  scent"}, {"version": "1", "index": 505, "hash": "94cdda57a1bef19d58bfa6a074623d6a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lluvia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "rain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 506, "hash": "7342dc31516318a469cfc6eb04eeddfe", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ej\u00e9rcito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "army"}, {"version": "1", "index": 507, "hash": "5a5a6871f96d0670ff2ad2684640056c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tren", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "train,  convoy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 508, "hash": "283f8cba1b44b0df51b2852c8c1b6288", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "c\u00edrculo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "circle,  club"}, {"version": "1", "index": 509, "hash": "56b777069dcf0ad0e113f1ac3cf3f652", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ventaja", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "advantage,  benefit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 510, "hash": "655bd50b2d4d9a77bdff70250cb13dfa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "isla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "island"}, {"version": "1", "index": 511, "hash": "159c7903e07352576010b9393e5849dd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "torno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "en torno a: about,  regarding"}, {"version": "1", "index": 512, "hash": "22e50a0d885aab3dc40a5dff63f20579", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "amistad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "friendship"}, {"version": "1", "index": 513, "hash": "9c9752fd8c878f87d8b52e927ba218ab", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cadena", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "chain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 514, "hash": "ee06332b111c6a3d6a592aa0438bcbe4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pol\u00edtico", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "politician"}, {"version": "1", "index": 515, "hash": "d2b3ea2dfddc40efdc6941359436c847", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rey", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "king"}, {"version": "1", "index": 516, "hash": "6f2c1bd846479c26b572c4327544a8f0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00e1nimo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "zest,  spirit,  heart"}, {"version": "1", "index": 517, "hash": "09384990d224366b7267422dca868aa4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "trato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "treatment,  manner,  agreement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 518, "hash": "e4741c1b8ff11436a616f321cb6e300f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ejercicio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "exercise,  practice"}, {"version": "1", "index": 519, "hash": "d7f2d5928e7c390284ca329cd9f1fd70", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "organizaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "organization"}, {"version": "1", "index": 520, "hash": "31bd7d583099c1afdf7091605db3012e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "agosto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "August"}, {"version": "1", "index": 521, "hash": "09ca0d5095609fe35bb7c9c7246e3cae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "secretario", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "secretary"}, {"version": "1", "index": 522, "hash": "5d0a6767924944db426b281dc4e0ed4c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dedo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "finger,  toe,  digit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 523, "hash": "25cb331f1c50581e089408cd7e5d1287", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gasto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "expense,  expenditure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 524, "hash": "07117fe4a1ebd544965dc19573183da2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caf\u00e9", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "coffee,  caf\u00e9"}, {"version": "1", "index": 525, "hash": "604e61493edd0dff778b879cea53f848", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "di\u00e1logo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dialogue,  conversation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 526, "hash": "40b366e9ff9d55de12b08d44e85215d8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "discurso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lecture,  discourse,  talk"}, {"version": "1", "index": 527, "hash": "f705d354cdd1209a9a766bbe23bd084b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hermana", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sister"}, {"version": "1", "index": 528, "hash": "936400f151ba2146a86cfcc342279f57", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caja", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bank,  box,  safe"}, {"version": "1", "index": 529, "hash": "730bf5afe8461798096a78db2a567d2c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "juez", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "judge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 530, "hash": "e5dee84f405b9366f44feef46df9704d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "particular", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "particular,  detail,  individual"}, {"version": "1", "index": 531, "hash": "3bbe4b9e755ea800eedca8ecb45117ea", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poeta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "poet"}, {"version": "1", "index": 532, "hash": "59e0f98e11ce2f78e2073a15e2a373f0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sorpresa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "surprise"}, {"version": "1", "index": 533, "hash": "1ac2434548f4ab66dcc22de295b5f332", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ventana", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "window"}, {"version": "1", "index": 534, "hash": "c22b2e53461ce57f2ffc6079bcd20ee0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caracter\u00edstica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "characteristic,  aspect"}, {"version": "1", "index": 535, "hash": "dce704fd8aa775365f1168c59dc4d9ad", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "suma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sum,  amount,  summary"}, {"version": "1", "index": 536, "hash": "2c6f68f1d2abd8e4b027a8a297b994b4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "volumen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "volume"}, {"version": "1", "index": 537, "hash": "adfa815c610440c705500f41a4355309", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "estaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "station,  season"}, {"version": "1", "index": 538, "hash": "545c04d28c2a5dd0812c6a1a4260db3e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "argumento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "argument,  plot"}, {"version": "1", "index": 539, "hash": "34ebded5b1f1ac01f281da7b6e289bbe", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "categor\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "category"}, {"version": "1", "index": 540, "hash": "e0b95c145bd9ef5d82e5a97f87f41a54", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "plata", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "silver,  money"}, {"version": "1", "index": 541, "hash": "5e87701e28efe1e2cbf7b6a683eb3f63", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conflicto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "conflict"}, {"version": "1", "index": 542, "hash": "a7dbf5ab6da4e3b41e4a6fecc7e6f7c3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "avi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "plane,  airplane,  aircraft"}, {"version": "1", "index": 543, "hash": "e18e642b37ba4f7983baaa05d035d958", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ropa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "clothes,  clothing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 544, "hash": "32bd3b82800c20c82f979e3cf1b26917", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "examen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "examination,  exam"}, {"version": "1", "index": 545, "hash": "1a869d4a7c61b4efc6dd13afbb163c9a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "habitante", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "inhabitant"}, {"version": "1", "index": 546, "hash": "daead462cb45c12e18731c2f91d09cae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "justicia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "justice,  fairness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 547, "hash": "1fee2754454857183ae3347ad129c272", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "criterio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "criterion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 548, "hash": "a6bd5f8f1d42005e9295ff815a0cb720", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "plazo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "deadline,  installment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 549, "hash": "327a35a652418454c3e9256c8ab2a005", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "kil\u00f3metro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "kilometer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 550, "hash": "8b42a1c9b8f9fde869f83c954b3d463b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hospital", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hospital"}, {"version": "1", "index": 551, "hash": "4b62746a24ffda4237953007eec4d473", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "satisfacci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "satisfaction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 552, "hash": "86aa0eab194b5fe69e3c1706b4c041d9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "silla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "chair,  seat"}, {"version": "1", "index": 553, "hash": "b173a89eccaa803e080cda9d44595372", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "juventud", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "youth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 554, "hash": "113a7f0c601f3d56b2cf4c9cca5ce636", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "acceso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "access,  entry"}, {"version": "1", "index": 555, "hash": "f5888d0bb58d611107e11f7cbc41c97a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "marco", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "frame,  mark,  setting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 556, "hash": "c0f0fddf35f129db4c5c51491ef29b2f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "prensa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "press"}, {"version": "1", "index": 557, "hash": "921897c5550abad041712b36cde062f8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "excepci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "exception"}, {"version": "1", "index": 558, "hash": "f1a0df45da9ed10ed88b07da013c8ec2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ausencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "absence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 559, "hash": "e0e9beb2348b197f48dcaf6b2b335b01", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sombra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "shade,  shadow"}, {"version": "1", "index": 560, "hash": "d5d814344ef08932750b2a1eb920938a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "profundidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "depth,  profundity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 561, "hash": "d40a937c6a3fc87e2d5b5cec7c0caf95", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "leche", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "milk"}, {"version": "1", "index": 562, "hash": "0dcd47deff532eeff275253d39aa2960", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "consideraci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "consideration,  regard"}, {"version": "1", "index": 563, "hash": "153697b4d766ede6971ee05a9d42e86c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "premio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "prize,  reward"}, {"version": "1", "index": 564, "hash": "6d4379b75ea90d264246df89def4277d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nacimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "birth,  origin"}, {"version": "1", "index": 565, "hash": "9e8354fefdf8dd9fdd6da8089cc7e281", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "invierno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "winter"}, {"version": "1", "index": 566, "hash": "af44718c08b70af311a78ecdfcff348f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "diciembre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "December"}, {"version": "1", "index": 567, "hash": "ff7e1c9ca0045ae630e85cf9da31665d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comportamiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "behavior,  conduct"}, {"version": "1", "index": 568, "hash": "b8b1b418007395b23b652e0556c3001b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cr\u00edtica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "criticism,  critique"}, {"version": "1", "index": 569, "hash": "8f6f4e8072f8e89ffd21759cf54218d8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fuego", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fire,  gunfire"}, {"version": "1", "index": 570, "hash": "d9edcc7223ff33e92fe0074c336347be", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tendencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tendency,  style"}, {"version": "1", "index": 571, "hash": "a6d44ea5029b4901c675606309ae79af", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "norma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "standard,  pattern,  norm"}, {"version": "1", "index": 572, "hash": "4f774cdb33865ad20778292614dee1e8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rueda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wheel"}, {"version": "1", "index": 573, "hash": "373fc283b674f863cd241a219241f046", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "puente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bridge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 574, "hash": "f27f0f1e71fede6d860dc9a07a1023ae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rasgo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "feature,  trait"}, {"version": "1", "index": 575, "hash": "9955fbdfa09ad83bf5f7283c170a66d7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "story,  tale"}, {"version": "1", "index": 576, "hash": "a01e4eff3d493726d06f9a8b47c866be", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "signo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sign,  mark,  symbol"}, {"version": "1", "index": 577, "hash": "138a3b6ec52800d8b79416e2081f6d2e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "se\u00f1al", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sign,  mark,  token"}, {"version": "1", "index": 578, "hash": "6160e311608f731013faf4952cd6a7eb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "campa\u00f1a", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "campaign"}, {"version": "1", "index": 579, "hash": "086ff137f78b3660079e101db54faae2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "puerto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "port,  harbor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 580, "hash": "d1d0f023f07f538e9a0a0f010c722b85", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aventura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "adventure"}, {"version": "1", "index": 581, "hash": "a9412f8dc03b7d4df1438c489cd2d25c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "marca", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mark,  brand,  trademark"}, {"version": "1", "index": 582, "hash": "f2c438410ac9ef36bcda416c28f353f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ilusi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "illusion,  hope,  dream"}, {"version": "1", "index": 583, "hash": "570f8e40738a1bca5d841bfeb6bfc05f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "compra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "shopping,  buy,  purchase"}, {"version": "1", "index": 584, "hash": "6b25cff77f9bad60a73fa81daa7d06ae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "inteligencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "intelligence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 585, "hash": "b626ef0376442a05f44fe4c838c20746", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "virtud", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "virtue,  quality"}, {"version": "1", "index": 586, "hash": "97c3dbafde8999f34a0bc423ca14106e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "remedio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "alternative,  cure,  solution"}, {"version": "1", "index": 587, "hash": "d2fbf1f66eb549e8220efd8962b120af", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "territorio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "territory"}, {"version": "1", "index": 588, "hash": "d2271f2c88a561cd64d07fa5eb4b3fc8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "facultad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "faculty,  ability"}, {"version": "1", "index": 589, "hash": "8aa6a366656863589ceb7a8d90a88acb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fotograf\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "photograph"}, {"version": "1", "index": 590, "hash": "ee180d8420b672941ecc2f3e5d990890", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "techo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "roof"}, {"version": "1", "index": 591, "hash": "20070af5f2dfba771a71b6945a05e2f7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conducta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "conduct,  behavior"}, {"version": "1", "index": 592, "hash": "52cb39fd78a403d8662e568a95e5aec2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "salto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "jump,  hop,  skip"}, {"version": "1", "index": 593, "hash": "96ac0342a3ccf9553e3d4c9da9b821b0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pan", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bread"}, {"version": "1", "index": 594, "hash": "4316f556748bb34b60a6fd70e501cac5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "disposici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "disposal,  disposition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 595, "hash": "958153f1b8b96ec4c4eb2147429105d9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "general", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "general"}, {"version": "1", "index": 596, "hash": "e382fa9c1631cba5cf37dd37a260d0d7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "disciplina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "discipline,  subject"}, {"version": "1", "index": 597, "hash": "0be5a6c82893ecaa8bb29bd36831e457", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "personal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "personnel,  staff,  staffing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 598, "hash": "0db323d57455f4c637b2a00ec7c5d15b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "columna", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "column,  spine"}, {"version": "1", "index": 599, "hash": "c546d5be87a27f72ea47cc749f47254c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "indio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "Indian"}, {"version": "1", "index": 600, "hash": "70b783251225354e883a5bef3c011843", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cat"}, {"version": "1", "index": 601, "hash": "c2340053515931e35149540fd295a0d3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "margen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "edge,  margin,  border,  brink"}, {"version": "1", "index": 602, "hash": "d45af0d1000a7c15dbc2d9eb058d0b52", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "resistencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "resistance,  opposition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 603, "hash": "f5eb7cacc3cafefe7ba36cb80a201819", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "p\u00e9rdida", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "loss"}, {"version": "1", "index": 604, "hash": "5fa6ce1b2e4798db96df0d628aa2d29d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tratamiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "treatment,  processing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 605, "hash": "27be43c12277d9dca6c36077b674e089", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "entrevista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "interview,  meeting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 606, "hash": "15d8febabf59d5a0029c8b2ac4e75e47", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "espect\u00e1culo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "spectacle,  show"}, {"version": "1", "index": 607, "hash": "041d24f96584b42c6029f5c5856d44ad", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "personalidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "personality,  celebrity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 608, "hash": "8980773d4785a8bdec7235f58934d60b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mayo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "May"}, {"version": "1", "index": 609, "hash": "6a43ace90fc8993467209b71bbb9b4f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "representaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "representation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 610, "hash": "1bab7a007f320ad7237d7a2699f6c7db", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "r\u00e9gimen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "regime,  diet"}, {"version": "1", "index": 611, "hash": "3377b830f7089f0c0847d42990177480", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "punta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tip,  point"}, {"version": "1", "index": 612, "hash": "ae1feb6d399876f2d17e6ae126e0762a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alegr\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "joy,  happiness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 613, "hash": "ff4e71fa594fa9bd559e0eaaf3da9b1e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "misi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mission,  task"}, {"version": "1", "index": 614, "hash": "12a77af4bf8f3f2d6d9a22065c7d07d3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "empleo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "work,  job,  occupation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 615, "hash": "6c7d8e8cb45d3f49c35b5deba9a280cb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "participaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "participation,  involvement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 616, "hash": "acb7000fc3ee490d9faf5b314bf0b3d2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "per\u00edodo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "period,  time"}, {"version": "1", "index": 617, "hash": "bba38af8cfcef973e8f3817b90c5fed3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "busca", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "search,  hunt"}, {"version": "1", "index": 618, "hash": "b22ddec8c1484dd211c63128f7d695a4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "superficie", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "surface,  area"}, {"version": "1", "index": 619, "hash": "1b89cf2b64f0afcdaeb79c366c13046d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pasi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "passion,  desire"}, {"version": "1", "index": 620, "hash": "e0223a9d58792ddce8d97046b10162b1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "veh\u00edculo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "vehicle,  car"}, {"version": "1", "index": 621, "hash": "e59abcbf368e95ff31f1f28dc4fa5fe2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "enero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "January"}, {"version": "1", "index": 622, "hash": "10af90684b158b96f221d51c3c08bff0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cap\u00edtulo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "chapter"}, {"version": "1", "index": 623, "hash": "cc5b73b4ed27f7923a5fc7f3ec0307e4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fracaso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "failure,  collapse"}, {"version": "1", "index": 624, "hash": "4210f7636e40006b57253e49163d0eef", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "experto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "expert"}, {"version": "1", "index": 625, "hash": "024cbc491f211568561265d146a412db", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "inquietud", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "restlessness,  anxiety"}, {"version": "1", "index": 626, "hash": "568d07e4192053f892eda22f5e8661cb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "organismo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "organization,  organism,  (human) body canci\u00f3n song"}, {"version": "1", "index": 627, "hash": "32d3d96e821fb253468b3d77e535fec4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "religi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "religion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 628, "hash": "f7b391b19acafeb16ba6f1e4676a617e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "departamento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "department,  apartment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 629, "hash": "91f62fa476b639243f51af8ccdaa6723", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "periodista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "journalist"}, {"version": "1", "index": 630, "hash": "2dae71b0e852e2554741d52a5f31073c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "interpretaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "interpretation,  interpreting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 631, "hash": "dccfde88780a07caedf97395cc71a640", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "belleza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "beauty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 632, "hash": "9accd4fca049d37780248024f4d2f156", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "universidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "university,  college"}, {"version": "1", "index": 633, "hash": "66c3ba9c65f12a5f3fa84cbcf7c48406", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "riqueza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "riches,  wealth"}, {"version": "1", "index": 634, "hash": "50dac7d217e184ff5791a175ba51f9f8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "moment,  while,  time"}, {"version": "1", "index": 635, "hash": "fe5323d5e54e115aa8e6099c1d960985", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "equilibrio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "balance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 636, "hash": "f9e012ff0bbbf0c385910af0795786c9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fruto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fruit,  result"}, {"version": "1", "index": 637, "hash": "e6d046ab5eed4dbf37b85cafafb0883d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "representante", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "representative"}, {"version": "1", "index": 638, "hash": "3322b7e366cd8de62c52052e05360350", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "exceso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "excess"}, {"version": "1", "index": 639, "hash": "d57a9571a48d025d40e87d16066a0628", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "capa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "layer,  coat"}, {"version": "1", "index": 640, "hash": "bc310c716144fa33d2801fc7395393c3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "defecto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "defect"}, {"version": "1", "index": 641, "hash": "71786854d894914e0614b58de0c35689", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "f\u00e1brica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "factory,  manufacture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 642, "hash": "22794111cd8954900374e6e0c2bd6f14", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "espalda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "back (body)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 643, "hash": "7c91b19a4dd897de47b37d0e38a5e28b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "g\u00e9nero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sort,  gender,  genre"}, {"version": "1", "index": 644, "hash": "802b8386dae626a9f258a656982160ea", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "econom\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "economy,  economics,  thriftiness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 645, "hash": "bfbac701b2eea507fa6f0cf877e31d4f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "bosque", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "forest"}, {"version": "1", "index": 646, "hash": "eeb92ca1a9a9647e0949cb3843a93ffb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "paisaje", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "landscape"}, {"version": "1", "index": 647, "hash": "5e97152112e0a05b8b0926c4b59c5093", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llamado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "call,  calling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 648, "hash": "d243800a7d0ba0f87081bcdd832bb05f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "paciente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "patient"}, {"version": "1", "index": 649, "hash": "0f3ec51ccafae6bdc4c2fe1af74aecb2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tensi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tension,  stress,  strain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 650, "hash": "e8912d27c62855d197f0d331fb8d12eb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ministro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(government) secretary,  minister"}, {"version": "1", "index": 651, "hash": "d35e409ca334d14379a89286b3041639", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "impulso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "impulse,  momentum"}, {"version": "1", "index": 652, "hash": "3bb9f7c241f35a769ecca64f80af3d04", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comercio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "commerce,  trade"}, {"version": "1", "index": 653, "hash": "d39867dcc5e0c9f0e11a40c54864beb3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "espera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wait"}, {"version": "1", "index": 654, "hash": "f012253814c311e2c6975382bcbdc51c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reserva", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reservation,  reserve"}, {"version": "1", "index": 655, "hash": "45e6d18d7e894a7c38888d75f3c0fcdd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "competencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "competition,  contest"}, {"version": "1", "index": 656, "hash": "2db250fe91182892ff4bc005b2431a57", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "observaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "observation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 657, "hash": "fbefc990f0e382b9282829f3ed20bd78", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vac\u00edo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "emptiness,  void"}, {"version": "1", "index": 658, "hash": "c3c06e5aa01129eea3b7ce3faf9de1c2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cifra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "figure,  number,  amount"}, {"version": "1", "index": 659, "hash": "ed836fb851ac679b75b5ba2f7335936c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escala", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "scale,  ladder,  rank"}, {"version": "1", "index": 660, "hash": "38b1e94fd101af9d68acbe52169edfd0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "procedimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "procedure,  proceedings"}, {"version": "1", "index": 661, "hash": "200d4293a9ab394107b3aeb950bae3cd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "f\u00f3rmula", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "formula"}, {"version": "1", "index": 662, "hash": "7bdb57228bb37f7890c47ac4c5538306", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00e1mbito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sphere,  space"}, {"version": "1", "index": 663, "hash": "7ea1741b60d49fa4ec336863ae3845a1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "informe", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "report"}, {"version": "1", "index": 664, "hash": "24aa825bbe6ab2c03c68693b17be4ee1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dimensi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dimension,  size"}, {"version": "1", "index": 665, "hash": "4983a0ab83ed86e0e7213c8783940193", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cliente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "client,  customer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 666, "hash": "dbf79b735691dd77144ec70af78270a0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "manifestaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "protest,  manifestation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 667, "hash": "d3401cacf87221ecb1fe4f93b8bb90cd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pico", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "y pico: and a bit; beak,  peak"}, {"version": "1", "index": 668, "hash": "2527f2b7e1788ecc776d278fb4b4e024", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sensibilidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sensitivity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 669, "hash": "71862c05ceaaea05710426d40ab1a47f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "regreso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "return"}, {"version": "1", "index": 670, "hash": "ee9cf3b7ac113ccd7af311804b2be8ff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "temperatura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "temperature"}, {"version": "1", "index": 671, "hash": "c027636003b468821081e281758e35ff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "julio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "July"}, {"version": "1", "index": 672, "hash": "892528e3dc04c9901ec1d89176c07e62", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "bomba", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bomb,  explosion,  pump"}, {"version": "1", "index": 673, "hash": "54f40b17e5885e6754ddbff125152cfb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00f3rgano", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "organ"}, {"version": "1", "index": 674, "hash": "7d4193110fe83a471ad24c08e9c37d05", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "avance", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "advance,  progress"}, {"version": "1", "index": 675, "hash": "9f549826f21b961f479491ebae283721", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "humanidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "humanity,  mankind"}, {"version": "1", "index": 676, "hash": "6fa8e2d8ab3f0f8512546ff1c100370e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "firma", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "company,  signature,  signing"}, {"version": "1", "index": 677, "hash": "0cda03eeec83dc9e6073cb19ac234a97", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "soldado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "soldier"}, {"version": "1", "index": 678, "hash": "091bdc9e09a07e55e7bb14c8f4348ecf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "clima", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "climate"}, {"version": "1", "index": 679, "hash": "6b855badf270bac63998d3285ef4b554", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "emoci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "emotion,  excitement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 680, "hash": "64f1c685a5271435b1e6d07e601a3e63", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "autom\u00f3vil", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "automobile"}, {"version": "1", "index": 681, "hash": "749dfe7c0cd3b291ec96d0bb8924cb46", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "evil"}, {"version": "1", "index": 682, "hash": "36468448d03e866f5cfba185ce76777f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "habilidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "ability,  skill,  talent"}, {"version": "1", "index": 683, "hash": "c42d42390a188ae884e05f21178aba39", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "identidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "identity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 684, "hash": "00b54ca709a8767e669e7cca81858fb6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "desgracia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "misfortune,  bad luck"}, {"version": "1", "index": 685, "hash": "3d56eb4a68de80aeba42404e1a5544c4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "deber", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "duty,  obligation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 686, "hash": "a1e05ee2564dbf16b04f09a23d482d06", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cola", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "line,  queue,  tail"}, {"version": "1", "index": 687, "hash": "e7a532d879e5f62d7c3f3edc8d513fe2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "progreso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "progress"}, {"version": "1", "index": 688, "hash": "1fbc6b28e8594d78953feabfc1afcc6f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "muestra", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "proof,  sample,  sign"}, {"version": "1", "index": 689, "hash": "5570d9813333f7b8d8c5a4bad9b78abb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "h\u00e1bito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "habit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 690, "hash": "934632d52710f0f95f727a4f04ae250b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mecanismo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mechanism"}, {"version": "1", "index": 691, "hash": "6ad2bc44724f764235d75ec75c642b9e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vivienda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "housing,  dwelling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 692, "hash": "c671226351fff07b668e4148654296c0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00e1rea", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "area,  zone"}, {"version": "1", "index": 693, "hash": "6abc795254fecc645b47d433b082a4a6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mezcla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mixture,  blend"}, {"version": "1", "index": 694, "hash": "9fe294e84d74be3955e9e425eef8965c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "habitaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "room,  bedroom,  habitat"}, {"version": "1", "index": 695, "hash": "b3e4d5a17006cdebc105954210e06587", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "instrucci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "instruction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 696, "hash": "51d22e3a36a8f7fe9adb644e7f205079", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "versi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "version,  account"}, {"version": "1", "index": 697, "hash": "b4eb480ebdcbd115bc2f4647dd21cf36", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lujo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "luxury"}, {"version": "1", "index": 698, "hash": "6bf587e8c39aa89ff54b753022f77fd6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "intervenci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "intervention"}, {"version": "1", "index": 699, "hash": "062118dc95f315ccf7200a4b1f17e52e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llegada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "arrival"}, {"version": "1", "index": 700, "hash": "71dfd553d8c25a1e9e7b6bded1a4f08c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alrededor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "surrounding area,  vicinity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 701, "hash": "00da973e131b6117c035608677a9cadd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "testigo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "witness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 702, "hash": "d3df207223e55dd1370ed405d78ce59a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dominio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "power,  control"}, {"version": "1", "index": 703, "hash": "363bcb0ad5353a45ec79ff95cd60d2be", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "raza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "race,  lineage"}, {"version": "1", "index": 704, "hash": "61c03a03516f763ed8fda05b01995e20", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "descubrimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "discovery"}, {"version": "1", "index": 705, "hash": "708c6e728167488cb02f5c26145954ae", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vacaciones", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "vacation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 706, "hash": "16a74f3241a0b6e4ff761b79a908745f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "provincia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "province,  region"}, {"version": "1", "index": 707, "hash": "2bde79bff687ae45f1354cde4324ccdd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "saber", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "knowledge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 708, "hash": "f2b8c07c3a0c9506c2c578afd0047f4f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "claridad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "clearness,  clarity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 709, "hash": "f2f645b7cf0962908fdb5bb485bd0cad", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "arena", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sand"}, {"version": "1", "index": 710, "hash": "37e2909a38e202474ccfbb4d55678fcf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "postura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "posture,  position,  attitude"}, {"version": "1", "index": 711, "hash": "6556e3491fc8f64266ce27cff5095916", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sal\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hall,  room"}, {"version": "1", "index": 712, "hash": "19ae8540c95ffe281df0ffd2e00eda3e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "escenario", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "stage,  setting,  scene"}, {"version": "1", "index": 713, "hash": "5f44b105ffaa16dbfdd6f548e6b64001", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "largo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "a lo largo: throughout; length"}, {"version": "1", "index": 714, "hash": "e919c49d5f0cd737285367810a3394d0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hotel", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hotel"}, {"version": "1", "index": 715, "hash": "a7bfc738b277afdef7f1a31dc6b033a4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "oficio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "job,  occupation,  function"}, {"version": "1", "index": 716, "hash": "f71b8edcb2425bd8f6a0474e90ab0010", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fila", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "line,  row,  file"}, {"version": "1", "index": 717, "hash": "b519fd16aa9afd9ab8bfa0acee34379c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "patr\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "employer,  landlord,  patron saint"}, {"version": "1", "index": 718, "hash": "f60c08ac6711c00a40cf694ddfd4a54b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pecho", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "chest,  breast"}, {"version": "1", "index": 719, "hash": "1a07afe7fc2c54d466d12569f05fb391", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tienda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "shop,  store,  tent"}, {"version": "1", "index": 720, "hash": "64369f62fd5aee6366731fc002f0cf9b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "protecci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "protection"}, {"version": "1", "index": 721, "hash": "cc7a84634199040d54376793842fe035", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "funcionario", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "civil servant"}, {"version": "1", "index": 722, "hash": "66a976b4ae5b592fb6cff6b772e4403e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "transporte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "transportation,  transport"}, {"version": "1", "index": 723, "hash": "bda9643ac6601722a28f238714274da4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "red", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "network,  net,  system"}, {"version": "1", "index": 724, "hash": "50fcabdf0797bcc6614774cebe630f36", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ca\u00edda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fall,  drop,  falling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 725, "hash": "4621dd08d8452ad13df5b30b29e5b9b7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "valle", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "valley"}, {"version": "1", "index": 726, "hash": "919a120beb46bc063e977ffdfd2bc50c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vuelo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "flight"}, {"version": "1", "index": 727, "hash": "de2d4dba9ca94e7cd4fc69c426449b11", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sexo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sex"}, {"version": "1", "index": 728, "hash": "5dd21d165429eb171d042dde55f5d768", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "iniciativa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "initiative"}, {"version": "1", "index": 729, "hash": "26750eac65cbd601b9d3749b7cfb0df5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "concentraci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "concentration,  gathering"}, {"version": "1", "index": 730, "hash": "7d9f114b6f511e314a3407f07137e208", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "grito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cry,  shout,  scream"}, {"version": "1", "index": 731, "hash": "913e596204060390c06f363b73e8e166", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "essence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 732, "hash": "99281303f6eab9edf2ec9f7ffde1bbaa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cocina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "kitchen"}, {"version": "1", "index": 733, "hash": "12f3123382ede0cdd2c1f2b0d806dbdf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reflejo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reflection"}, {"version": "1", "index": 734, "hash": "d0ba56874e4795ce60b41cb0b835816d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "definici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "definition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 735, "hash": "5edd1d545293e50c8fa562a0ef357925", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "abogado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lawyer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 736, "hash": "e0ab631b3191718c76a407a7133994f4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sesi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "session,  meeting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 737, "hash": "6ea8c44896933605cb8b3b65c941b44a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reloj", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "clock,  watch"}, {"version": "1", "index": 738, "hash": "73c4219f117c610d09bd24c752086380", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "muchacho", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "boy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 739, "hash": "f0c30d57409bdfba4d6a211456a2ec59", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "octubre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "October"}, {"version": "1", "index": 740, "hash": "ce3ad4969ac349833ff188364b73ca19", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "exposici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "exhibition,  display"}, {"version": "1", "index": 741, "hash": "f207fdc51fab89887c0197e66c5f8290", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ingreso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "entrance,  admission,  income"}, {"version": "1", "index": 742, "hash": "211e969daa1ba8469cd46ce2591fc7b9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dibujo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "drawing,  sketch"}, {"version": "1", "index": 743, "hash": "439fa3b6291b7cd2a7714288395c5010", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hueso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bone"}, {"version": "1", "index": 744, "hash": "354b4ea2a961d1716e3e44a99ad6940c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "militar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "soldier,  military person"}, {"version": "1", "index": 745, "hash": "59417166c47f7e6b70d1a6701bf4efdd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "motor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "engine,  motor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 746, "hash": "df0d91bcb908fd5bb53fd6694962e3dc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "oposici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "opposition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 747, "hash": "02794e781b898030fa84265a9062acaa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "patio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "courtyard,  playground,  yard"}, {"version": "1", "index": 748, "hash": "233926cc509b0d57b7188653097d1eec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fruta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fruit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 749, "hash": "b3bfb5ad6ba04daf0f8f1930133d89dd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ideal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "ideal,  goal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 750, "hash": "8e62561c3ac6d3fb0016e9a34a2caa5d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "actor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "actor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 751, "hash": "2a450aa68536369868ccd389f77469ac", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "confusi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "confusion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 752, "hash": "932872c3ad7fe56e507748cf859b3cad", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "traje", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "suit,  dress,  costume"}, {"version": "1", "index": 753, "hash": "fc4bdeb8bc8e4ca9a27e624286c4543d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "exigencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "requirement,  demand"}, {"version": "1", "index": 754, "hash": "c24b2517a24b406e544220208bd032d9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "v\u00edctima", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "victim,  casualty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 755, "hash": "047c0a4204cd03f3d5ebe04de02e7ab3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "playa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "beach,  seaside"}, {"version": "1", "index": 756, "hash": "293c7f6869d9a851b7509d9d3efcebc4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "trabajador", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "worker,  laborer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 757, "hash": "901a6060cb4ba6f27157ac9af5addbe1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hierro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "iron"}, {"version": "1", "index": 758, "hash": "b58805f51a4bffac8760ade5bc530d74", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tela", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cloth,  fabric"}, {"version": "1", "index": 759, "hash": "09dc70b7e2eff387b7b13849eae77018", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "producci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "production"}, {"version": "1", "index": 760, "hash": "ab85f491d0bc4fbdfa552f1082844234", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "febrero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "February"}, {"version": "1", "index": 761, "hash": "e89dfd94f0bcaeea44e47208b02cce4d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "s\u00edmbolo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "symbol"}, {"version": "1", "index": 762, "hash": "b2f7ab0ac61dd0c305e0f896ef1fb12e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "medicina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "medicine"}, {"version": "1", "index": 763, "hash": "07be375c621f65111df2a6d030f48bdd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "b\u00fasqueda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "search"}, {"version": "1", "index": 764, "hash": "7c50251943786913177ff30b74a20e97", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tranquilidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tranquility,  peace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 765, "hash": "ace97f138b6af702720d01cd149ada48", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "espejo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mirror,  reflection"}, {"version": "1", "index": 766, "hash": "73230fe07833a236dd9044683f4998cb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comprensi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "understanding"}, {"version": "1", "index": 767, "hash": "ef1cb281e8d66dd60792f36019ace6a4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cerebro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "brain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 768, "hash": "5c9b82a4a4042b7b26902b6c8242c510", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tiro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "throw,  shot"}, {"version": "1", "index": 769, "hash": "4a7df6c4d7a607c6ba0beaf34012c1fa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "abuelo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "grandfather"}, {"version": "1", "index": 770, "hash": "acfaf891f87043206366a960213dc0b1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "declaraci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "declaration,  statement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 771, "hash": "31e2822c40382c57b67312dbefbdf706", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sujeto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "subject,  individual"}, {"version": "1", "index": 772, "hash": "fe6c35dc28a3efed220a6ba60d842e37", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ense\u00f1anza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "teaching,  instruction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 773, "hash": "a30f3f79678725865e3fd6bd2f910aba", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "permiso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "permission,  permit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 774, "hash": "bd23eba8a6d62b672d28c090368615b3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "evoluci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "evolution,  development"}, {"version": "1", "index": 775, "hash": "c32ad523b2f2e06562af4de793b9df73", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "t\u00edo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "uncle,  guy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 776, "hash": "796597dabee7ee2d78aa677c282aea0b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "moral", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "morals,  ethics"}, {"version": "1", "index": 777, "hash": "362e9d05adac79dd99d210ca27bca17c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "parque", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "park"}, {"version": "1", "index": 778, "hash": "e7e56b85c07fbbec2099a681e15e39e9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ingeniero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "engineer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 779, "hash": "9fc856708aa30cf9c23a8bfbd4f0fee8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "borde", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "edge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 780, "hash": "3c1f670565fdc02148da4e105deed4b2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "entusiasmo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "enthusiasm"}, {"version": "1", "index": 781, "hash": "8dd329389531f662a87e57dbbcabad5b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "independencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "independence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 782, "hash": "513985c6a0ef65e7ba4094bd11be41e7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mentira", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lie"}, {"version": "1", "index": 783, "hash": "36fffee0826956c7898054153eb866b2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sueldo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "salary,  pay"}, {"version": "1", "index": 784, "hash": "68bd2395b0ba0f06b15e5db290bca94d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comparaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "comparison"}, {"version": "1", "index": 785, "hash": "fa472db1114a7e002c4edcd25ab9bc27", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "seno", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "breast,  bosom,  cavity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 786, "hash": "1e587b5f7e9f33b6485937d441551685", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "canto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "singing,  chant"}, {"version": "1", "index": 787, "hash": "24f98d6452da30f83615c9eade9ac1db", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "potencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "power,  potential"}, {"version": "1", "index": 788, "hash": "d72139a450ab630f5ce886bfe1299ebf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "oficial", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "official,  officer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 789, "hash": "39e3c3d3cbf9064e35f1bee7dbd176f8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fortuna", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fortune,  fate"}, {"version": "1", "index": 790, "hash": "fbd9c64a0e9e3ec499bdef181042bdba", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "crimen", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "crime,  murder"}, {"version": "1", "index": 791, "hash": "6cc610dccc275a08449cb9cff790b42a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ciudadano", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "citizen"}, {"version": "1", "index": 792, "hash": "dc258235abfd18858e6fa97d7f13f376", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ba\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bathroom,  bath,  swim"}, {"version": "1", "index": 793, "hash": "23ee4cc4445d9188dc50657a53bc0e11", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reconocimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "recognition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 794, "hash": "5120ba408f775df5636f2cb9e46fc65c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "exterior", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "exterior,  outside"}, {"version": "1", "index": 795, "hash": "ed14bced025bb9e653b8a21da27cccf3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cr\u00e9dito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "credit,  reputation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 796, "hash": "fc64a31c7bbdd0192a91ff14e98f110d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "alternativa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "alternative"}, {"version": "1", "index": 797, "hash": "4709ead2b0079d2d9ae797c94baf3e2a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "canal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "channel,  canal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 798, "hash": "f77538d26d37221483971c3323d5f050", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "agente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "agent"}, {"version": "1", "index": 799, "hash": "66d70610b684db4b9d2417f6da614a60", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pago", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "payment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 800, "hash": "57f1ffeb62056c70d065760601e4813f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "filosof\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "philosophy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 801, "hash": "dd381a050f1987e7b5c7b73296fd49a5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lector", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reader,  lecturer"}, {"version": "1", "index": 802, "hash": "ec9a8063dd7a6a064cf70c4a7e5e3d14", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "triunfo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "triumph,  victos"}, {"version": "1", "index": 803, "hash": "dc123bc5cca365682f932f5a785dd240", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "s\u00e1bado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "Saturday"}, {"version": "1", "index": 804, "hash": "836821929cb02aade5072aec0c1aa93c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "amiga", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "friend (f)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 805, "hash": "d4ec738181a8c0901e0ce4bd68442645", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "carretera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "highway,  road"}, {"version": "1", "index": 806, "hash": "e0e34c5ad05aac3eef6ab31eacbf7a5c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "victoria", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "victory,  triumph"}, {"version": "1", "index": 807, "hash": "19382e77faa9a0b511f875c8f5c3bd11", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "p\u00e1jaro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bird"}, {"version": "1", "index": 808, "hash": "686d4ba6996ab7e2bd626c9a3cc965c6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "biblioteca", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "libran"}, {"version": "1", "index": 809, "hash": "f6f4050fd163002429121b93e6e0b06b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reflexi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reflection"}, {"version": "1", "index": 810, "hash": "bcf5c490527ba5cff2197b7c16e211a7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vocaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "vocation,  calling"}, {"version": "1", "index": 811, "hash": "a91e4e0cf303cb9b16316ffd896a914c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "continente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "continent"}, {"version": "1", "index": 812, "hash": "3cbec8a1fe8edd4edb94302f95f45188", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tabla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "chart,  board,  table,  plank"}, {"version": "1", "index": 813, "hash": "f437d19934abdb39fc3f66a95adcc325", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ensayo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "essay,  rehearsal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 814, "hash": "8e4c8500fb823b206d2e96b9e5fc96ca", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "plato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "plate,  dish"}, {"version": "1", "index": 815, "hash": "eaa59957f4c42a89fc353c5cc11a42de", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "jard\u00edn", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "garden"}, {"version": "1", "index": 816, "hash": "ea22de91aa14f0bd063ee8b22e55caec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "imaginaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "imagination,  fantasy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 817, "hash": "b0ae8eda9b838b9f4f3285cb6adfe9cb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poes\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "poetry,  poem"}, {"version": "1", "index": 818, "hash": "8891f19e45b76350c7108ae4c8950e84", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "guardia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "guard,  watch,  lookout"}, {"version": "1", "index": 819, "hash": "ca023d46d231e4bfb69a27e83a396a99", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "privilegio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "privilege"}, {"version": "1", "index": 820, "hash": "ae442b3ec02781e25f556cee2bb3eec3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "monte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mountain"}, {"version": "1", "index": 821, "hash": "85da01cb2e5b2e08469a2791cdd1b6ce", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "precisi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "precision"}, {"version": "1", "index": 822, "hash": "fbd0f4af2828db21b02614c421803e3d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sacrificio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sacrifice"}, {"version": "1", "index": 823, "hash": "6e9dd081f0ab25f3b57813790988f662", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hilo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "thread,  yarn,  wire"}, {"version": "1", "index": 824, "hash": "3e886a8e6b4d2b7ce926862ec7c16330", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aparici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "appearance,  apparition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 825, "hash": "81b75a8bcf86f672bae52143067486d6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "poema", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "poem"}, {"version": "1", "index": 826, "hash": "56dce5f99d88b9cf954fe21694e3a6d3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "curiosidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "curiosity,  quaintness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 827, "hash": "3c0d6899e1e6d98fa3e3932b3491adbe", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "diente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tooth,  cog"}, {"version": "1", "index": 828, "hash": "25c8fd756b4871e9295440291f1b22fe", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "primo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cousin"}, {"version": "1", "index": 829, "hash": "d00e33236b1047aa2108715fbc7cfd8a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "apariencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "appearance,  aspect"}, {"version": "1", "index": 830, "hash": "823419b28997e72b63c13cd5b2a3474b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "novedad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "latest news,  newness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 831, "hash": "d2ac473559323489421747601740046c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "castigo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "punishment,  penalty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 832, "hash": "7e84b442f353cc4c27e90b0271e82b03", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "carro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "car,  cart"}, {"version": "1", "index": 833, "hash": "ad6cc3e161e1d5e53fb14d0ab1642b7d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aumento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "increase,  rise"}, {"version": "1", "index": 834, "hash": "ee78024a64e4ab8426d6aa0d1967c800", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pobreza", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "poverty,  lack,  scarcity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 835, "hash": "034615c220c975510e958a93358143c5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "d\u00f3lar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dollar"}, {"version": "1", "index": 836, "hash": "f5ddaf0ca7929578b408c909429f68f2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "local", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "place,  quarters"}, {"version": "1", "index": 837, "hash": "94479ee29cbadaa69626fbd1a455e09e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "industria", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "industry,  factory"}, {"version": "1", "index": 838, "hash": "b9ce8959c05554155460a5730b604d09", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "caballero", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "gentleman,  knight"}, {"version": "1", "index": 839, "hash": "4a5bbe99369cdb08914537c709a5b545", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "especialista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "specialist"}, {"version": "1", "index": 840, "hash": "2f8a31d0a3d1e511a15329fb6144e3a1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "temporada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "season,  period,  time"}, {"version": "1", "index": 841, "hash": "7a5b5501705f07767ec8bed743855a01", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "humor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "mood,  humor"}, {"version": "1", "index": 842, "hash": "170c7ecfc24dedf0ff39abaf54d0d918", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "naci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "nation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 843, "hash": "ef4f3d00f44433ace9ce1895bf8b6486", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "felicidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "happiness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 844, "hash": "e5115cdc8c35f6429bfe39b4b37f376a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "amante", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lover"}, {"version": "1", "index": 845, "hash": "47a2bc61c4a889cd9bb37f2ec3c16725", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "c\u00e1lculo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "calculation,  calculus"}, {"version": "1", "index": 846, "hash": "3db965653d3e76a95e531bf6fef5ebb7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "composici\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "composition,  make-up,  essay"}, {"version": "1", "index": 847, "hash": "2d0788cebe6e9fcc36da12fa6d64f71c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rapidez", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "speed,  velocity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 848, "hash": "448b55f2fa8c2960deeaa64a9929a692", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "huevo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "egg"}, {"version": "1", "index": 849, "hash": "ae3f40ec4270b3dc9e67437bd5907a6a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "crecimiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "growth,  increase"}, {"version": "1", "index": 850, "hash": "fbc71ce36cc20790f2eeed2197898e71", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "clave", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "key"}, {"version": "1", "index": 851, "hash": "89087f75c2a0b5e3abd9c32c58ba2487", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tragedia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tragedy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 852, "hash": "2d963b923538180aca7fe7b10ec35e26", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "colecci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "collection"}, {"version": "1", "index": 853, "hash": "0409ee1a3f104ce0c18bdcc6642c5800", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "chica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "girl,  female"}, {"version": "1", "index": 854, "hash": "235d4e02914a755c936363f1d1a34530", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "prestigio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "prestige"}, {"version": "1", "index": 855, "hash": "635277b171f80ca3923fad8a5c552ad6", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "secci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "section,  cut"}, {"version": "1", "index": 856, "hash": "9cdebedc790703b7e743a005a984e478", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "bolsa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bag,  purse,  stock exchange"}, {"version": "1", "index": 857, "hash": "c3653e4408832e6611f37dcd90544de8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cinta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tape,  ribbon,  film,  strip"}, {"version": "1", "index": 858, "hash": "135df6308f6656871211da6c0072da0c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cuello", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "neck,  collar"}, {"version": "1", "index": 859, "hash": "980f1881eebd9970b5a5ecb35b8ff3f3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "continuaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "continuation,  follow-up"}, {"version": "1", "index": 860, "hash": "dccefc9affe37ba60b49d0a4789ce042", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "abril", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "April"}, {"version": "1", "index": 861, "hash": "be06fe026b4329ae24e95fdc995a134b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "actuaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "performance,  acting"}, {"version": "1", "index": 862, "hash": "742f32c65ffd18b766fa307f8de2d47d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "factor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "factor,  cause,  influence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 863, "hash": "919bb07ab517924d399ec1e523fb7bf4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esquina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "corner"}, {"version": "1", "index": 864, "hash": "cb38ee49f9d097896af9d92e9cdac2f9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "hombro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "shoulder"}, {"version": "1", "index": 865, "hash": "e531f738345f218f845adae22b3bdfab", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "infancia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "infancy,  childhood"}, {"version": "1", "index": 866, "hash": "bd707d2b0fb0fe634bb1a05e76285b83", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "descanso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "rest,  interval,  break"}, {"version": "1", "index": 867, "hash": "272b5eb31e1c7ff85a96f076fbea4d17", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "zapato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "shoe"}, {"version": "1", "index": 868, "hash": "d84e71d2af7aaf01484063b73052d5b0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "parecer", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "opinion,  looks"}, {"version": "1", "index": 869, "hash": "cd8193113f5c74760eeb2531430e43c3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "familiar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "relative"}, {"version": "1", "index": 870, "hash": "27bc26060aba31028005ee49c6003645", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "m\u00e9rito", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "worth,  merit"}, {"version": "1", "index": 871, "hash": "8f2beee1780ab78f1e69e4475375484d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "muro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(outer) wall,  rampart"}, {"version": "1", "index": 872, "hash": "3fd5a88217e3e3bb0b9d54b655dd92f3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mont\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lot of,  heap,  pile"}, {"version": "1", "index": 873, "hash": "d78acd9cad41bf3b3a0aaa3b4b106c4e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "disco", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "disc,  disk,  record"}, {"version": "1", "index": 874, "hash": "b7f3288ebe26785e377252db854ce8f3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "demanda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "petition,  request,  demand"}, {"version": "1", "index": 875, "hash": "c9396331df9111ee1734c397fa16ae06", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mueble", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(piece of) furniture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 876, "hash": "5a375afbbc13846f13867f041840258a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "desastre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "disaster"}, {"version": "1", "index": 877, "hash": "e201994dca9320fc94336603b1cfc970", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "secreto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "secret"}, {"version": "1", "index": 878, "hash": "7c63611b6b71e8461328579153850211", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "angustia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "anguish,  distress"}, {"version": "1", "index": 879, "hash": "84384a402c9540e35b23819f42b745ec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nube", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "cloud"}, {"version": "1", "index": 880, "hash": "9e7a7265e053b3689413d069b57fb779", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "miseria", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "misery,  wretchedness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 881, "hash": "b9d0fec848160add9fbc8749e556d47e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "significado", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "meaning"}, {"version": "1", "index": 882, "hash": "e8b61d5e9e22d58e97ba1c7827aa8864", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fama", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "reputation,  fame"}, {"version": "1", "index": 883, "hash": "1f9c75dcfc2fbbf839b961435ea950b3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "palacio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "palace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 884, "hash": "47a2047bfe670bd2a7dd96b124d79348", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "o\u00eddo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "hearing,  ear"}, {"version": "1", "index": 885, "hash": "1bbf40cb75e404eec00eec0bc14c5d13", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "polvo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dust,  powder"}, {"version": "1", "index": 886, "hash": "9dba8c62be85eeace5e733ed6b974ecc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sacerdote", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "priest"}, {"version": "1", "index": 887, "hash": "1b0999daad7f5a4cfb1f0a2a87edee14", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "lecci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lesson"}, {"version": "1", "index": 888, "hash": "84109ae4b4178430b8174b1dfef9162b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rosa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "rose"}, {"version": "1", "index": 889, "hash": "95eeaab62bdd8499a271aa10dcedfbfc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "olor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "smell,  odor,  fragrance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 890, "hash": "e35ee65e2d18185dd790c7f34bf0a615", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "contrato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "contract,  agreement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 891, "hash": "3bbcbc9ff3bd73364829500fc3f4e33f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "presentaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "presentation,  introduction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 892, "hash": "d981f1307d5608514a1212c92b7ff047", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "c\u00e1rcel", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "jail,  prison"}, {"version": "1", "index": 893, "hash": "b507fd587a985b37b549307148e09a2b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "divisi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "division"}, {"version": "1", "index": 894, "hash": "3b2a8505276383bdb14227e51adab54e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rev\u00e9s", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "al rev\u00e9s: backwards,  upside down"}, {"version": "1", "index": 895, "hash": "3ca148f6130e8ed960324c1ee8f10cca", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cualidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "quality,  attribute"}, {"version": "1", "index": 896, "hash": "58d6b418f96c6b689f84a45f2f99f2a3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "\u00edndice", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "index,  forefinger"}, {"version": "1", "index": 897, "hash": "52b073c34b10fb26da4b6f099273841e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "marzo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "March"}, {"version": "1", "index": 898, "hash": "ebb466827173e8ba62ecfb1fcdc9c23c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "atm\u00f3sfera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "atmosphere,  environment"}, {"version": "1", "index": 899, "hash": "9772370be8dae4e7e0118e8648667407", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "planeta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "planet"}, {"version": "1", "index": 900, "hash": "83dc2f83c61558791a0961d0bf4edca8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "orgullo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pride"}, {"version": "1", "index": 901, "hash": "4a2fff6e24e75e9e26ca2decc0ead091", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "jornada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(working) day,  shift"}, {"version": "1", "index": 902, "hash": "b50347c6fa8e55d5b562fe0f1511d324", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "palo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "stick,  pole"}, {"version": "1", "index": 903, "hash": "cee39bef6c213e43d30a0632d960a42f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dise\u00f1o", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "design"}, {"version": "1", "index": 904, "hash": "9a9b0020b19c328b751e2bffde40f63d", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "l\u00f3gica", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "logic"}, {"version": "1", "index": 905, "hash": "4458edd8baf7005c414cdc879bf87811", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "herencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "inheritance,  legacy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 906, "hash": "f060f2a89fb79ea767721ce14b349b0c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "deporte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sport"}, {"version": "1", "index": 907, "hash": "c68694892859e2f05020bc4b2f2af56f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "reina", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "queen"}, {"version": "1", "index": 908, "hash": "16dcb52511a7608b49438325a3909c86", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "bandera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "flag"}, {"version": "1", "index": 909, "hash": "c46bfcafeb0bc33d809a80fd392bd3a2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "maravilla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wonder,  marvel"}, {"version": "1", "index": 910, "hash": "c157cd3cfba5c444f2f0e6378f3da47e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "banda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(musical) band,  sash"}, {"version": "1", "index": 911, "hash": "6bbea091fbcbe4770f208a628cd1d8b5", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cristal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "glass,  crystal,  window"}, {"version": "1", "index": 912, "hash": "203efce5e225d5b1895b1cf9c8bb8cba", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "an\u00e9cdota", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "anecdote"}, {"version": "1", "index": 913, "hash": "0bbbc1c65f58f5fa69059d43427063ff", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "leyenda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "legend"}, {"version": "1", "index": 914, "hash": "bc3b8f53cc07e015b9a3b6060991ca58", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "muerto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dead person"}, {"version": "1", "index": 915, "hash": "79a603dd22d496d37a0bbb8639fc52dd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "az\u00facar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "sugar"}, {"version": "1", "index": 916, "hash": "c030d4bdccb0776ffdea2a2df5820116", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "inclinaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "slope,  incline,  tendency"}, {"version": "1", "index": 917, "hash": "2d2be6d41ac10b74d95de100c20bec68", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rostro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "face,  countenance"}, {"version": "1", "index": 918, "hash": "2e48df4f7c40a091b6fb63f6782aa1b8", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "separaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "separation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 919, "hash": "e434dd9c7f573fb03924e0c4d3d44d45", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "eco", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "echo,  response"}, {"version": "1", "index": 920, "hash": "ebea7d75ce0ae38a0440221a067eb2bc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cita", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "appointment,  date,  quotation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 921, "hash": "8ccfe5bb94209840a96dd30763cee4a9", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "actualidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "present (time)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 922, "hash": "07c8fdff50f593aa69adc1a3a97d7f40", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "fantas\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "fantasy,  fancy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 923, "hash": "8fdf9c2cfaf0f10d3e21496bd23ca3fa", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "promesa", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "promise"}, {"version": "1", "index": 924, "hash": "40c8cf865328b964d85bfc798faa46a1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pata", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "leg,  paw"}, {"version": "1", "index": 925, "hash": "66c9eed121277d8be2df09ce25c4687a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "foto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "photo,  picture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 926, "hash": "5840aba2ea35524910088d1e7b8357dc", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "administraci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "administration"}, {"version": "1", "index": 927, "hash": "88a0376e3aab4b5fb5d43ee3c11745c2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "civilizaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "civilization"}, {"version": "1", "index": 928, "hash": "fb327beb0edf676dbe614f4cc6773b72", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ocupaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "occupation,  use"}, {"version": "1", "index": 929, "hash": "151fc541ef24733a098642cd03ca7225", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "asiento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "seat,  chair"}, {"version": "1", "index": 930, "hash": "47c3da0dc1d88b7721e3905d8a4b5f76", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "pista", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "clue,  track,  trace"}, {"version": "1", "index": 931, "hash": "d3b3b3da624de708973c9f3d28cd31a2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "testimonio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "testimony,  evidence"}, {"version": "1", "index": 932, "hash": "e3d3e231ea7b7267f355d2b3363f0111", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "regalo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "gift,  present"}, {"version": "1", "index": 933, "hash": "a763325082a2a758cc0e60115fbac26c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "contradicci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "contradiction"}, {"version": "1", "index": 934, "hash": "86094b61cb9f63b77f982ceae03e95f0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "metal", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "metal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 935, "hash": "d8cbc34059d74a1717ded8d5b1d4dd30", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "aceite", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "oil"}, {"version": "1", "index": 936, "hash": "f59512f027dea3ea404d375b68c059cd", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "c\u00f3digo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "code"}, {"version": "1", "index": 937, "hash": "fb809ff2f5dd772ff6fc15d447474773", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "uni\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "union"}, {"version": "1", "index": 938, "hash": "70ad9daaac2267c6bfd5d0baa50f1025", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "extensi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "extension,  area,  expanse"}, {"version": "1", "index": 939, "hash": "9008aeedf063af1a4589e1c64684aae1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "duro", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "duro (money)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 940, "hash": "c1c6583dafa1e596ada7f8f21e301737", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "var\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "male,  man"}, {"version": "1", "index": 941, "hash": "6471911aeb4b705b8ff6c21841a58ce7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "evidencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "evidence,  certainty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 942, "hash": "432cfc6d8280d4ed96392b89bfe5cd8b", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dignidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "dignity"}, {"version": "1", "index": 943, "hash": "c88da23de6738cc20c35c566cd0c407e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "esc\u00e1ndalo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "scandal"}, {"version": "1", "index": 944, "hash": "0cd84b4d36912da616ee5655204282f7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "colega", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "colleague"}, {"version": "1", "index": 945, "hash": "019598bbc4a553858bb03f4d26d4e772", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "horario", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "schedule,  timetable"}, {"version": "1", "index": 946, "hash": "c30d57c5282945f16d2893c09fe975bb", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "orilla", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "shore,  edge"}, {"version": "1", "index": 947, "hash": "176c6d1f1a6e9a081156eb87c9bc3300", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "copia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "copy"}, {"version": "1", "index": 948, "hash": "846f42970f762c94a7fba05ea4707224", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "huella", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "trace,  track,  footstep"}, {"version": "1", "index": 949, "hash": "56cd8c56b20a625bc532de0e3c130944", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ejemplar", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "copy,  issue"}, {"version": "1", "index": 950, "hash": "6a618ea0f7ee3f41f7c1b4f4cb767794", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cura", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "priest (m),  cure (f)"}, {"version": "1", "index": 951, "hash": "0bf5e363db87c4eff270d5d6de343a2f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "garant\u00eda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "guarantee,  warranty"}, {"version": "1", "index": 952, "hash": "dffa97e9dd82533832f4c58bc285dc5c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vaso", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "(drinking) glass,  vase"}, {"version": "1", "index": 953, "hash": "9019cbe4458150159d9cc2f1cd473cf1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "perfil", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "profile,  outline"}, {"version": "1", "index": 954, "hash": "a230e6288e6410e468424619955c1526", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "proporci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "proportion"}, {"version": "1", "index": 955, "hash": "26b3d316d986e32019a6d1b3d00bdbcf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ceremonia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "ceremony"}, {"version": "1", "index": 956, "hash": "613cc50e18903dd4e8a4c198ac6c4d81", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "vidrio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "glass,  pane"}, {"version": "1", "index": 957, "hash": "7382f3fcc232228a26760954c6f9a236", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "ruta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "route"}, {"version": "1", "index": 958, "hash": "df0fb39243e8a7b228c18b183a446007", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "anuncio", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "advertisement,  announcement"}, {"version": "1", "index": 959, "hash": "e2946d6c7dc5e292bd84fb68bb4e8bcf", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "soledad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "loneliness,  solitude"}, {"version": "1", "index": 960, "hash": "04a3511fb91e3313ee47aae4731cfc7a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "tesis", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "thesis,  exposition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 961, "hash": "d00f8d8226b7749b7a9d40a260ca3ab4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "rinc\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "corner,  nook"}, {"version": "1", "index": 962, "hash": "500570d14dee04ee16dc5e55cd5862b7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "nariz", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "nose"}, {"version": "1", "index": 963, "hash": "0a70f0c5a3548f7641369440ca52347a", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "bolsillo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "pocket"}, {"version": "1", "index": 964, "hash": "e46249e1a9ff74c7d87a00ddc6f898e4", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "asociaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "association"}, {"version": "1", "index": 965, "hash": "f366d2db3a9995e6e2ae2cad19beeb09", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "mando", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "command,  authority"}, {"version": "1", "index": 966, "hash": "e26d3232c1136fd194865e41415cf3f3", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "sabor", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "taste,  flavor,  sensation"}, {"version": "1", "index": 967, "hash": "5ea0338c4e2c30683b6a6095cffdbbf7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "d\u00e9cada", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "decade"}, {"version": "1", "index": 968, "hash": "5e7a4d03abfc9dbfe007bd667e939f13", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "preparaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "preparation,  training"}, {"version": "1", "index": 969, "hash": "07493aa6f31d8b728c8160637e4827ac", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "afecto", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "affection,  fondness"}, {"version": "1", "index": 970, "hash": "e6eeaf4bb7c86562493dff5599f7bb6c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "protesta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "objection,  protest"}, {"version": "1", "index": 971, "hash": "634b1b907d31425f890340853a81a9a2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "patria", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "native land,  fatherland"}, {"version": "1", "index": 972, "hash": "aaac3c07daad4c5b43001787171bd971", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "consumo", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "consumption"}, {"version": "1", "index": 973, "hash": "ca676b517a4cee2da0ccbd208a051173", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "selva", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "forest,  jungle"}, {"version": "1", "index": 974, "hash": "32772bfcca5ee4e4d5d79f087280b3b7", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "deuda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "debt"}, {"version": "1", "index": 975, "hash": "7b9e4513221c86d6443a452d270a4652", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "horizonte", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "horizon"}, {"version": "1", "index": 976, "hash": "b67885ab956f9d8f8946768f2e362e92", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "talento", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "talent,  skill"}, {"version": "1", "index": 977, "hash": "fee74eac0728a1bb5ff7d4666f8c4a88", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gas", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "gas"}, {"version": "1", "index": 978, "hash": "8ab25a55645f132e945b79f3011a53f0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "t\u00e9", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tea"}, {"version": "1", "index": 979, "hash": "8d281a60d6d637903d4eccd26ddb0104", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "gloria", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "glory,  fame"}, {"version": "1", "index": 980, "hash": "6eb67e3155abcb9e647ea2fbb8178386", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "noviembre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "November"}, {"version": "1", "index": 981, "hash": "91decb248f8a7be12263b3988d28cdf0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "candidato", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "candidate"}, {"version": "1", "index": 982, "hash": "94dfe0ec1c717475b86f4db71de554ba", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "llave", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "key,  faucet,  wrench"}, {"version": "1", "index": 983, "hash": "c21da5ebde28f5b281565a58cc591d18", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "inconveniente", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "inconvenience,  drawback"}, {"version": "1", "index": 984, "hash": "7cc050ea04bc71b41b09ba90c98c51e0", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "af\u00e1n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "eagerness,  zeal,  effort"}, {"version": "1", "index": 985, "hash": "2920781af780c8fdb046180eed1c7c79", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "etc\u00e9tera", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "etcetera"}, {"version": "1", "index": 986, "hash": "69bb5c63d2b712b0fc2a4ba4af07a5ec", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "comisi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "commission,  committee"}, {"version": "1", "index": 987, "hash": "55861e647650fd42bae14c332d33f80e", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "posesi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "possession"}, {"version": "1", "index": 988, "hash": "f3ee63690ca1bf0d72cf1ed60904a24f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "dama", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "lady,  dame"}, {"version": "1", "index": 989, "hash": "3e73e3378f7c81e5b0f08b332e42d77f", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "onda", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "wave,  ripple"}, {"version": "1", "index": 990, "hash": "f17ed833132a190c1907db8bbdf19e39", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "botella", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "bottle,  flask"}, {"version": "1", "index": 991, "hash": "2a54c96a018815eecba59519c81c6009", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "torre", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "tower"}, {"version": "1", "index": 992, "hash": "175c2ca79cf195e1d143ea62aa4e998c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "combinaci\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "combination"}, {"version": "1", "index": 993, "hash": "5e2dd4fa352aee717e2a64ded72dae54", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "cad\u00e1ver", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "corpse,  body"}, {"version": "1", "index": 994, "hash": "b36f324ac27c7f91fcae2bfd8d72737c", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "paquete", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "package,  packet"}, {"version": "1", "index": 995, "hash": "24007dcf03169ce4f0d147ae4c7a1b28", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "apellido", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "last name"}, {"version": "1", "index": 996, "hash": "18de638f7c4b808947156d34083ca3a2", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "conferencia", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "conference,  lecture"}, {"version": "1", "index": 997, "hash": "1ca5e8125c3802cbcca76db710eb6d01", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "propuesta", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "proposal,  proposition"}, {"version": "1", "index": 998, "hash": "caac2c4418b33dbbf346e35a36fd9187", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "intensidad", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "intensity,  force"}, {"version": "1", "index": 999, "hash": "1db888b7c41262604644efedebc0afb1", "questionType": "text", "questionText": "explosi\u00f3n", "hintType": "none", "answerType": "text", "answerText": "explosion"}]